<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Memo | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/memo/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2014-05-14T11:34:45+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exchange Dream by Jiaqian]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/04_26_exchange-dream-by-jiaqian.html"/>
    <updated>2014-04-26T01:46:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/exchange-dream-by-jiaqian</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The first day in Guangzhou City, there is the Exchange Dream by Jiaqian.</p>

<p>So when I went to Sun Yat-sen University to join in it.</p>

<p>It is my second time to take Guangzhou Train. And when got there, I didn&rsquo;t know where is north. So I thount and found it by the building&rsquo;s  window(You know although in sourth of China, people still build the big window to sourth).</p>

<p>And with the map, I found the university. But I did not get it, so I asked a passby, he told me the position.</p>

<p><img src="/images/guangdong/sunyatsen.jpg" alt="sun-yat-sen-university" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>So I went to the classroom where the Exchange Dream started. I foung it before the activity started. And I was hungry, though I had a Niunan Noodle on the road to train stop, the noodle tasted really bad. So I asked a girl where is refectory or dining hall.</p>

<p>She gave me a direction but it is not very clear. Then I went out of the classroom to the refectory.</p>

<p>I did not found it, I walked back and asked a passby. She told me she went there too that I can followed her. And we went the refectory together.</p>

<p>On the road, we talk a few things about the Sun Yat-sen University , her major and why I was here.</p>

<p>Then I arrived in the refectory, I bought a meal ticket, and took some rice and some vegetables to eat(like Popeye the Sailor).</p>

<p>After the dinner, I went back to the calssroom. It is about 7 pm, but Jiaqian was still not arrive.</p>

<p>We waited for about 2/3 hour. She came. And I shared a story about my entering a higher school. And listend more stories from others.</p>

<p>The number of viewers in Sun Yat-sen is less than CUMT. But there are more interesting stories.</p>

<p>And the two girls who was left from me are just hign school students, so young and so cute.</p>

<p>A girl shared her childhood and love story, another girl shared her hairstyle and she how to bet with her deskmate, a boy just standed there until the activity stoped &hellip;
<img src="/images/guangdong/jiaqian.jpg" alt="exchangedream" />
After it, I went back by train. It is so late, so I took a shower, watche a little TV and just slept for tomorrow&rsquo;s test.</p>

<p>Oh there is a very cool thing in Sun Yat-Sen University, an old style&rsquo;s washing room.
<img src="/images/guangdong/wc.jpg" alt="wc" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[There is also a Mandela in China]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/12_10_there-is-also-a-mandela-in-china.html"/>
    <updated>2013-12-10T12:59:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/there-is-also-a-mandela-in-china</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Now, all over the world, there is a lot of activities to commemorate Mandela. Even in China, even In official  medium. And these official medium would emphasize to Mandela resist white people. But you know, <strong>pure Mandela&rsquo;s mind</strong> is to resist unfair not white people.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Obviously, in China there is a Mandela too. And China&rsquo;s Mandela&rsquo;s last name is Liu and Wei and Tan and &hellip;</p>

<p>And somenone we call him China&rsquo;s Mandela is still in the jail. I just want to say do not foget him.</p>

<p><strong>Do not foget the man who resist unfair like Mandela.</strong></p>

<p>Dead man is dead but alive man is alive.</p>

<p><code>May God Bless China!</code></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[为什么《人民日报》会引用洋葱的新闻报道？]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_28_730.html"/>
    <updated>2012-11-28T22:22:57+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/730</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>为什么中国官方的，身为喉舌的《人民日报》会引用美国不入流的洋葱社的新闻，为什么我们义务地为金正恩搞宣传？</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[如何培养出人才]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_05_705.html"/>
    <updated>2012-11-05T23:33:42+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/705</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>中国人一心想拿<strong>诺贝尔奖</strong>，就如同想拿奥运金牌、想举办奥运一样。结果呢，当你那了金牌、办了奥运。你才发现，其实你什么都没有得到，什么都没有改变。诺奖也一样。第一个拿诺奖的中国人（你我都清楚他不是莫言）。他拿到了，媒体也低调了，转变成了，要拿诺奖就拿<strong>自然科学</strong>上的诺奖，什么和平奖那是“工具”。不巧，2012年，<strong>莫言</strong>拿了一个非自然科学的诺奖，而且莫言不同于他拿些那非自科诺奖的中国人，他在国内，而且有“官职”，并且还是自由身。于是，一记耳光扇到了那些鼓吹拿自科诺奖的人身上，因为媒体开始盛赞莫言。我也顿觉害臊，为自己过去被灌进去的想法，以及还保留这想法的人害臊。</p>

<p>其实，我可以很负责任地说，<strong>中国人不会拿到诺贝尔奖（自科），而且我也真心不希望有人拿到</strong>。拿到了又有什么用，奥运办过了，你的生活改变了吗？没有，日子照旧——<strong>赚钱，娶妻，贷款，买房，还房贷……</strong>还要盼着<strong>别金融危机啊，印钞厂少印点钱啊</strong>！空洞的、无意义的生活将一直这样下去，不会因为某人拿了诺奖而改变。</p>

<p><strong>但是，什么能改变这些呢？</strong></p>

<p><strong>——教育。</strong><!-- more --></p>

<p>都说<strong>百年大计-教育为本</strong>。但看看，<a href="http://www.chinanews.com/cj/cj-gncj/news/2009/09-08/1856514.shtml">我国教育公共投入所占GDP比例</a>。你就会明白，一切皆为虚伪的扯淡。</p>

<blockquote><p>中国实际公共教育投入仅占GDP的<strong>百分之二点四</strong>，<strong>低于印度</strong>的百分之二点七，相当于美国的一半。</p></blockquote>

<p>上帝是不会一个不舍得向教育投入的国家拥有高素质国民的，也不会让这个国家拿该死的诺贝尔奖。所以说，<strong>第一点，如果想真心让这个民族变得强大，社会必须认识到如果不向教育投入更多</strong>，那么你不会拿到你想要的回报。当年，</p>

<blockquote><p>    楚国大举进犯齐国。齐王派淳于髡去赵国请救兵，携带黄金100斤，车马10辆作为出兵的交换条件。 　　淳于髡接到大王的口谕之后仰天大笑，齐王莫名其妙，问道：“你嫌东西少了吗?”
淳于髡忍住笑回答：“哪敢嫌少！”
齐王追问：“那你笑是什么意思?”
淳于髡回答道：“臣想起今早遇到一个人的可笑行为，故觉得想笑，绝无嘲笑王上之意。”
齐王问道：“今早有什么可笑的事发生，给寡人讲讲。”
淳于髡回答：“臣今天早上在上朝的路上，经过田野，看见有一个农夫跪在路旁祭田，他举着一只小猪脚爪，端着一盅水酒，嘴里振振有词地祝愿说：‘土地爷啊， 求你保佑，让我五谷满仓，猪牛满圈，金银满箱，儿孙满堂！’我见他手里拿的这么微薄，嘴里要求却那么奢厚，所以越想越好笑。” 　　.
齐威王听了很惭愧，便增加了黄金1000镒，白玉10对，车马百辆。让淳于髡带着这些东西到赵国求救。</p></blockquote>

<p><strong>第二点，教育需要自由。</strong></p>

<p><strong>        投入和产出永远不会出现反比关系</strong>。但是如果我们真的向教育投入足够多的钱了，中国就能拿到那诺贝尔的自科奖了吗？</p>

<p>显然不是，中国教育一直就<strong>欠缺自由</strong>，如果没有<a href="http://www.ftchinese.com/story/001045722/?print=y">自由的环境</a>，根本不会有任何学术成就。上过学的人都知道，终你医生学习生涯，你的班级中，中小学，拥有<strong>最高权威</strong>的是你的<strong>班主任</strong>，大学拥有最高权威的是你的<a href="https://zh.wikipedia.org/wiki/%E6%94%BF%E6%B2%BB%E8%BE%85%E5%AF%BC%E5%91%98">辅导员</a>、你的教授。什么时候，人人都可以自由地<strong>顶撞</strong>教你书的人，什么时候这个民族的教育才会有希望。</p>

<p><strong>第三，学校需要办学的自主权</strong></p>

<p>自从秦朝建立以来，中国一直是一个中央集权的国家。中央集权的第一要务便是，<strong>下级服从上级</strong>。但谁都知道市长不会比村长更了解自己的村子。但决策却在上级手里。中国的教育也是如此，全国学校千篇一律，因为把学校办成什么样在上级手里，不在学校手里。</p>

<p><strong> 不得不说，还有一点，我们必须搞清楚我们要教出<a href="http://zqb.cyol.com/html/2012-10/10/nw.D110000zgqnb_20121010_1-03.htm">什么样的人</a>？</strong></p>

<p>我们不要书呆子，但是<strong>如今上学的人多少都有些呆气</strong>。我们不要量产出的廉价T恤，我们要让每一件都有不同的图案，穿在不同的人身上。这个东西叫个性，<strong>按照我的初中老师的话，“有个性是人的缺点”。</strong></p>

<p><strong>中国的教育制度很可怕，我时常能感觉到自己无法适应，或者说就不应该去适应。我如今是这样走过来的，我不希望我的后代也这样。</strong></p>

<p><a href="http://baham.co/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/76774514.jpg"><img src="http://baham.co/wp-content/uploads/2012/11/76774514.jpg" alt="虐童" /></a></p>

<p>（<strong>让我揪心的图片，谨以此图，纪念这个时代</strong>）</p>

<p><img src="http://wiki.sociallearnlab.org/images/b/ba/EduNext.png" alt="http://wiki.sociallearnlab.org/images/b/ba/EduNext.png" /></p>

<p><em>EduNext ｜教育前瞻”是一个由多个关注中国教育未来和学习型社会的网络社区共同发起的网络征文活动，在2012年10月10日起，至2012年11月10日结束， 为期1个月。我们也把这个月份称之为“中国教育前瞻月”。在此期间，你可以写作一篇或多篇blog帖子，阐述你对于教育和学习等话题的看法。请在［<a href="http://www.sociallearnlab.org/wiki/index.php?title=EduNext">http://www.sociallearnlab.org/wiki/index.php?title=EduNext</a> 这个页面]上“投稿文章”部分按格式提交你的blog帖子，你也可以直接在新浪微博上 @教育大发现社区 (<a href="http://weibo.com/sociallearnlab">http://weibo.com/sociallearnlab</a>) 提交你的blog帖子链接。教育是我们的未来。未来取决于当下。</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[娱乐之上-江南Style大集合]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/10_27_658.html"/>
    <updated>2012-10-27T16:03:45+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/658</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>1  娱乐之上-<strong>江南Style大集合</strong>-PSY &ndash; GANGNAM STYLE</p>

<p><embed src="http://player.youku.com/player.php/sid/XNDY3NTU5NjEy/v.swf" allowFullScreen="true" quality="high" width="480" height="400" align="middle" allowScriptAccess="always" type="application/x-shockwave-flash"></embed></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>2  娱乐之上-<strong>江南Style大集合</strong>-Korean dance team
3 娱乐之上-江南<strong>Style</strong>大集合-<strong>婚礼</strong>版
4 娱乐之上-江南Style大集PSY (ft.<strong> HYUNA</strong>) 오빤 딱 내 스타일</p>

<p>5 娱乐之上-江南Style大集合-<strong>GUNMAN STYLE</strong></p>

<p>6 娱乐之上-江南Style大集合-<strong>伊顿Style</strong></p>

<p>7 重庆南开中学 <strong>千人江南Style</strong></p>

<p>对此，我觉得，只有当学生能选择跳什么样的操时，中国才会有希望。</p>

<p>8 娱乐之上-江南Style大集合-Minecraft Style</p>

<p>9 MIT（麻省理工）恰恰版Style</p>

<p>10 香港Style（群星演出客串）</p>

<p>11 MIT 麻省理工 Style</p>

<p>由于网站迁移，请移步<a href="http://www.youku.com/playlist_show/id_18469431.html">这里</a>进行观看</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
