<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Memo | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/memo/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-08T00:53:22+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cross]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_23_the-cross.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-23T05:01:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-cross</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I bought a silver cross from taobao, at Novermber 11.</p>

<p>Before I went for the business trip.</p>

<p>When I came back to Dandong. I got the package. And wear it.<!--more--></p>

<p>But on Saturday, I lost it. When I found it is gone, it is 2 or more hours later. I think it is lost when I ride the bicycle to east.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catching Crabs]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/09_30_catching-crabs.html"/>
    <updated>2014-09-30T13:05:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/catching-crabs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Days ago, 2 roommates and I went to the China&rsquo;s side of Yalu River to catch the crabs in the evnening.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>And this is my first time to catch crabs. When I was a child, I had caught dragonfly, frogs and butterfly. But not crabs, for where I live is not near river.</p>

<p>Now, always feel that childhood is beaytiful.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bad Word]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/09_18_a-bad-word.html"/>
    <updated>2014-09-18T13:48:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/a-bad-word</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These days, I got cold. Today is the third day. And I say a wrong word. Orginally, I just want to say a joke. But I found it is bad a bad even evil word. Because I spoke so lordly that someone turn back to see my position.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I am not veru happy, bacause of the cold, the word from the Aunt in dinning hall(I asked her a lunch box, she refused.) and the others' talking about I using my left hand to eat.</p>

<p>In this time, to think the reson, it is nothing to make me unhappy, I feel.</p>

<p>And Jiao aksed me why use left hand? I wanted to say a joke, so say &lsquo;Why you have so much why?&rsquo; loudly.</p>

<p>It is not polite to her and others in the dinning hall though she did not care it. But I say it. And after the word, I felt really sorry.</p>

<p>I did a bad thing and said a bad word.</p>

<p><code>Therewith bless we God, even the Father; and therewith curse we men, which are made after the similitude of God.</code>  &mdash;James 3:9</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_10_driving.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-10T08:47:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/driving</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After I get the driving license, I neally ever drive.</p>

<p>But there is a chance for me to drive.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The day befor I take the Toefl Test, my siste and my brother in law came to join the wedding.</p>

<p>Although the driver, my brother in law try to avoid dringking, but it failed. And he need to work tomorrow, and my sister too.</p>

<p>So the driving burden came to me, I did not the lenth from my home to my sister and brother in law&rsquo;s apartment, but maybe 30 kilometers or more.</p>

<p>This is my first time to drive so far after I get the driving license.</p>

<p>Just write this article to remember this thing.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphone]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_01_smart-phone.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-01T08:59:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/smart-phone</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My old android phone is broken, it can not start up. I did not know why? Because when I pluged in its battery on the night. It still could work. But when I wake up, it could not start up.</p>

<p>So I just found out my old Windows Mobile phone, my first smart phone with 64Mhz cpu and 64M ram, but it rum more smoothly than most cheap android phones.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>But there is a problwem when I use the wm phone, cause it can not get a normal signal. The intensity it get is alwasy weak. So I need a new phone. Though I want to buy a new phone after I started to work originally.</p>

<p>The Nokia X is my first choice, because of Nokia&rsquo;s fame. But most of markets did not sell it. So I bought a samsung android phone. And it is cheaper than nokia x. Cause I just need an android smart phone which can run smoothly. This samsung phone is enough for me. And I can not afford an expensive phone. So I choose it.</p>

<p>Android, Firefox OS, Ubuntu Phone, Tizen &hellip; there are more and more phone os now. But the os I like mostly is wm.</p>

<p>Smooth, Light, though ms would not support it. Writing this article is to remember the OSes, and the smartphones I used.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
