<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Baham | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/baham/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2015-04-07T13:09:48+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What a Foolish Thing I made]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_07_what-a-foolish-thing-i-made.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-07T01:29:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/what-a-foolish-thing-i-made</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>  I talked at Hui&rsquo;s dormitory, Ning came to tell us Lei was fighted with others. And need someone to go to help him.</p>

<p>  After thinking this thing, I thought I would go with them.</p>

<p>  Then we went to Teachers' University. I did not the fighting thing&rsquo;s detail, but the aim I went is just to keep men calm down.</p>

<p>  But always thing you could not imageine happened.<!--more--></p>

<p>  Lijian is there, when we came, we went in the camp, and they just find the guy and kick him. I did not do this, cause I knew I came to make men calm. And Cheng/Cao/Hui either. What I thought is just that Lijian vent his anger on this. Then went back to school.</p>

<p>  After we left the camp, 4 men went on the TAXI, we others walked to wait other taxis, some guys run to catch us.</p>

<p>  2 were already on the taxi, and Cao said &lsquo;run&rsquo;. We run. We fime men run to a same direction.</p>

<p>  But they were on a taxi to catch us. What a fool, we went to the same direction. And I was caught up. Peng too. They asked me did I fight? I answerd no. Then to Peng, He said yes. And they took Peng. After the thinking, I left Peng and called others.</p>

<p>  Then we went back to Teachers' University, until we knew Peng is back. Finally, Peng is safe and sound.</p>

<p>  What a foolish thing I did, God will not like this, I did things by youth and without wisdom. THis is a lesson to me.</p>

<p>  And thanks God, keep me and anyothers from CUMT or from UT safe and sound.</p>

<p>  And when an unhappything happend, just please depend on God, and use your heart with love, and be patient.</p>

<pre><code>爱是恒久忍耐.
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[one accosting]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_30_one-accosting.html"/>
    <updated>2014-05-30T13:03:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/one-accosting</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A long time ago. It is a month&rsquo;s tenth day. I do not remember the date.</p>

<p>I was on the train home. And a girl sat on the left of me.</p>

<p>A pretty girl with a slim legs and a white sports shoes. I think she is a college student too just like me.</p>

<p>But you know I am shy to talk to others especially a pretty girl.</p>

<p>Nearly at the midnight, I could not fall asleep. And I found she did not either.</p>

<p>And <!--more-->
I struggle a few times and started the accosting, maybe this is the first accosting in my life. And screwed up my courage to ask her &ldquo;Which stop she will take off the train?&rdquo;</p>

<p>Just write an article to remember this. Nothing else. I think this thing is worth to remember.</p>

<blockquote><p>_&lt;</p></blockquote>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What will happen tomorrow?]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/02_23_what-will-happen-tomorrow.html"/>
    <updated>2014-02-23T05:51:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/what-will-happen-tomorrow</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My last seanson in CUMT will start. And what will happen?</p>

<p>In this winter festival. I got fever, wrote my article, watch TV and someting else. After I came to school.</p>

<p>I watch some US TV play and read some books.</p>

<p>And tomorrow nest season will start. What will happen?</p>

<p>What will change?</p>

<!--more-->


<p>&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;&mdash;Nothing.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[These Days I Write Just a Few Blogs.]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/10_27_these-days-i-write-just-a-few-blogs.html"/>
    <updated>2013-10-27T23:02:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/these-days-i-write-just-a-few-blogs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> In these days ,I need to find Job candidates to submit my resume,and I need to go to driving school to learn drive,and I replace mt Chakra Linux by Kubuntu,and configure my octopress blog,install softwares……</p>

<p>I feel tired,what I will do next,is go to class.and maybe tomorrow,I need to configure deja-dup to backup my files.</p>

<p>So these days I didn’t updated my blog frequently! But there is still a thing worth be happy,I have a new visiter who leave a commit. And may Gob bless you!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[今天做了一件好事也是一件屌丝气十足的事]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/09_24_jin-tian-zuo-liao-%5B%3F%5D-jian-hao-shi-ye-shi-%5B%3F%5D-jian-diao-si-qi-shi-zu-de-hao-shi.html"/>
    <updated>2013-09-24T20:34:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/jin-tian-zuo-liao-[?]-jian-hao-shi-ye-shi-[?]-jian-diao-si-qi-shi-zu-de-hao-shi</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>  今天，是科目3路考的日子，教练通知我们在八点钟到，大概八点零几分我到了，八点半多教练也到了，得知自己的组别后就赶往了考试候车地，早晨到现在，一直在下着不断的雨，雨不大，天气却很冷。号码排在前边的幸运了，因为可以不用在外边冻着，考完了，就走了，我是排在后边的，所以，心里有被冻感冒的准备，这时发现一个女生，年龄和我相仿，一直蹲在伞下边，初期没注意，以为蹲着是一种避风的方法。后来发觉不对，他一直捂着肚子。</p>

<p>  又过了没多久，第二批学员上车，她起来了，向前听了听教练和考完的人的经验分享，然后，发现她，径直向一个方向走了，本以为这是肚子疼，去厕所，目光随着她看了看，发现，她在一棵树旁在吐。当时我就突然觉得自己应该做点什么，因为从始至终，她没和谁说过话，应当是一个人在排队。</p>

<p>  其实之前就有上前询问她到底怎样，是否需要帮忙这类话，不过，怕她是“痛经”，一询问反到让两个人都尴尬，看她在树边吐，想想，这应当不是，我应该过去帮忙。   不过，心里还是有斗争，但最终，我还是决定应该走上前去，送给他一包手纸，仅此而已，不用说太多的话，简单两、三句即可，应该不会让自己的紧张显露太多，摸摸裤袋，纸就剩两张了，于是，我在她身边走过，一是当时有点胆怯，二是我应该买一包纸。回来的路上，我走到她，身边，弯腰问她：“你怎么了？”就把纸递过去了，——“我胃不好，天冷就胃疼。”，就这两句话，我就走了，其实，我还是紧张，不过，<strong>勇气只要通过瓶颈，话就出来了</strong>。</p>

<p>  她还是蹲在角落里，捂着肚子，我想，也许我应当好人做到底，就去前边不远的面馆里问老板，你这有热水吗？得知有，并且征得老板同意后，我把自己水瓶的水倒了（当时想天冷，不容易口渴），接了一瓶热水。回来，又走到她身边，说：“这有瓶热水，你可以敷敷肚子。”说得有点紧张，不过还是说了出去。</p>

<p>  其实，我不知道自己今天为什么会这么做？首先，我不善和女生，尤其是有点漂亮的同龄女性交谈，但我却鼓起勇气做了;其次，我明知这么做很有屌丝气，但我还是做了。</p>

<p>  这也许是上帝给我的改变，毕竟<strong>我要做个义人</strong>，而不要做一个罪人。</p>

<p>  无论这么做，多么像一个屌丝，但我还是做了。很多时候，我觉得现在人心不古，无论从《圣经》里的观点看、还是儒家的传统观点，这个时代，多数人都是罪人，因为这些人在能伸出援手时没有伸出、能给人阳光时却给了人黑暗或者乌云。耶稣差遣12门徒时说</p>

<pre><code>——“腰带里不要带金银铜钱。行路不要带口袋，不要带两件褂子，也不要带鞋和拐杖，因为工人得饮食是应当的。”
</code></pre>

<p>  想想古代，没有告诉交通工具的时候，普通人想要远行，要怎么办，我想那个时代，普通人在和平时远行，一定是一路受人接济，人接济人，出行是也受人接济，于是，所有人远行时，都能成功抵达目的地。</p>

<p>  但现在不同，如果有人夜里敲你的门，说“您好，我从XX来的，身上没钱了，能让我住一宿吗？”你会开门吗？</p>

<p>  我能做的且想做的就是<strong>在别人远行的路上给他提供帮助，然后他也会在别人远行的路上提供帮助……最后，我们所有人出行都不用带鞋、拐杖、和第二件褂子。</strong></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
