<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2014-07-12T03:40:22+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_10_driving.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-10T08:47:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/driving</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After I get the driving license, I neally ever drive.</p>

<p>But there is a chance for me to drive.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The day befor I take the Toefl Test, my siste and my brother in law came to join the wedding.</p>

<p>Although the driver, my brother in law try to avoid dringking, but it failed. And he need to work tomorrow, and my sister too.</p>

<p>So the driving burden came to me, I did not the lenth from my home to my sister and brother in law&rsquo;s apartment, but maybe 30 kilometers or more.</p>

<p>This is my first time to drive so far after I get the driving license.</p>

<p>Just write this article to remember this thing.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_10_driving.html">http://baham.co/07_10_driving.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toefl Test I Took.]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_10_toefl-test-i-took.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-10T08:02:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/toefl-test-i-took</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my first time to take Toefl Test. After I graduated and left the camp. I prepared for the toefl test. But I didn&rsquo;t prepared it well. I even not finished the one whole office guide test. It is really a pity. Wahtever, the porpose I take it is just verified my English skill, although the scores did not public, but the I achive the porpose, my English-skill is bad.</p>

<p>What I need do is learning and practicing.</p>

<p>The 4 parts in toefl, I nearlly did not finished one of them well.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>In Reading Section, After I finished the first one, I found I did not have enought time . And I feel nervous, and you know, many answers are guessed by me.</p>

<p>And the listening section, what I pay the muchest time to practice, but what I can understand is just a little. And I was too tired to concentrate on the convesations or lecture. This is a lesson, when you take the test, you must sleep well and enough.</p>

<p>Then it is speaking, I found I can not read the paragraphes on time. As for the questions about speaking by oneself, I could not prepare them well in 15 seconds. I need to practice thinking in the heart with English.</p>

<p>What is the last is Writing Section. Maybe it will gave me the best score in 4 parts. But you know, they are still not good articles, it&rsquo;s just like an articles that writen by a pupil. not like an article by a high school graduation.</p>

<p>What I need to practice and learn is very much.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_10_toefl-test-i-took.html">http://baham.co/07_10_toefl-test-i-took.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Train to the Dandong]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_08_the-train-to-the-dandong.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-08T01:55:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-train-to-the-dandong</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> I bought a train ticket from Heb to Dandng, though I can not get on the car in Heb City. Because I found I can buy a sleeper ticket from Heb, not from my hometown. So I bought this ticket.</p>

<p>A few days later, when I went to get the ticket, I found I mmade a mistake, the ticket I bought is a student ticket. But you know I am not a student anymore. So the functionary asked me for the student card, I could not gave it. So what I can do is getting a refund for the ticket. And buy a chair ticket from my hometown. What the puzzle I will face with is I need sit on a chair more than 9 hours during the night. It will make me tired.</p>

<p>Before I leaving home, I pray to God for my travel, my safety  and my job.</p>

<p>I arrived at railway station about 6 pm, but the arrving in the raiway&rsquo;s time is about 5 hours later. So I went to Wanda Cinema to watch <em>Transform 4</em>. Though the ticket is expensive.<!--more--></p>

<p>This is my first time to watch <em>Transform</em>.</p>

<p>When the time is up, I went to the station to get on the railway. When I was on the railway, I found the functionary said there is an opportunity to buy a sleeper ticket. So I queue, although there is someone jumping the queue, There is an amazing thing happen, I bought the sleeper ticket, the last one.</p>

<p>When I get the sleeper ticket, I went to the sleeper car. I through many sleeper cays. Some has a very bad smell from someone&rsquo;s feet. I said in my heart I do not want to meet the one with bad feet smell. Finally, it did. But I found another bad thing, someone near me  snored with a very big noise. I could not wake him up, we did not know each other. What I can do is praying, like Hu said his experience with his roommate, I pray for my sleep time. It worked, subway started, I fell in a sleep until the nexr day&rsquo;s morning.</p>

<p>And there was another thing happen, when I queue to buy the sleeper ticket, I bought the last one, The functionary said, I got an amazing phone number and the ID number and the ticket number. And you know I bought the last sleeper ticket.</p>

<p>Am I lucky?</p>

<p>No! It is all on God&rsquo;s blessing.</p>

<p>Because there is a word in Holy Bible&mdash;</p>

<p><code>Hitherto have ye asked nothing in my name: ask, and ye shall receive, that your joy may be full.  </code>  &mdash; John 16:1
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_08_the-train-to-the-dandong.html">http://baham.co/07_08_the-train-to-the-dandong.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphone]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_01_smart-phone.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-01T08:59:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/smart-phone</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My old android phone is broken, it can not start up. I did not know why? Because when I pluged in its battery on the night. It still could work. But when I wake up, it could not start up.</p>

<p>So I just found out my old Windows Mobile phone, my first smart phone with 64Mhz cpu and 64M ram, but it rum more smoothly than most cheap android phones.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>But there is a problwem when I use the wm phone, cause it can not get a normal signal. The intensity it get is alwasy weak. So I need a new phone. Though I want to buy a new phone after I started to work originally.</p>

<p>The Nokia X is my first choice, because of Nokia&rsquo;s fame. But most of markets did not sell it. So I bought a samsung android phone. And it is cheaper than nokia x. Cause I just need an android smart phone which can run smoothly. This samsung phone is enough for me. And I can not afford an expensive phone. So I choose it.</p>

<p>Android, Firefox OS, Ubuntu Phone, Tizen &hellip; there are more and more phone os now. But the os I like mostly is wm.</p>

<p>Smooth, Light, though ms would not support it. Writing this article is to remember the OSes, and the smartphones I used.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_01_smart-phone.html">http://baham.co/07_01_smart-phone.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Time To Read All Contents of Bible]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_25_first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-25T12:50:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tonight, I read the <em>Malachi</em>, the last one in Old Testament.</p>

<p>Since September 2013, I started to read Bible. And I finshed reading all content of Holy Bible.</p>

<p>Write this post to remember this day.</p>

<!--more-->


<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_25_first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible.html">http://baham.co/06_25_first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[back home]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_25_back-home.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-25T07:32:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/back-home</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The school ask us to leave by 6.23, I left at June 23. I wanted to leave at 21. But I change the plan to decide to leave at 6.23.</p>

<p>I took the railway and the taxi to home.</p>

<p>There are cleaner air in hometown than Xuzhou or other cities I had visited in China.</p>

<p>But you know the time to work is coming. So there is not much time for me to stay in hometown. And I still had a Toefl test to take.</p>

<h2>Guy from South China on Railway</h2>

<!--more-->


<p>When the railway is arriving My Province, the guy in a lower berth spoke something to another one. And I talked to him about trifles.</p>

<p>After the talk, I found goal is near my home. But the difference is that I need take a taxi, but he wanted to ride a bike to the destination. He graduate from Guangdong and worked in Nanjing before coming here.</p>

<h2>Girls near my berth</h2>

<p>There are 6 berthes right of my berth. After arriving my destination  I found there are 3 girls who knew each other, and 2 girls who knew each other, and 1 elder women who is not like a student. You know that 3 girls always talked. And I just listen, they talked boyfriend, wealth, life and so on. And you know it is a time to listen, to listen girls&#8217; thoughts and feelings.</p>

<h2>Family left of my berth.</h2>

<p>On the left of my berth, there is one family, one daughter, one father, and one mother. The daughter is just like me, graduated from college and went back home. They live in Liaoning Province. The daughter studied in Nanjing. And theis pronunciation is kind of like Ma.</p>

<h2>Summary</h2>

<p>This travel maybe is the my last travel from Xuzhou. My students who still in Xuzhou they saw me off, and Sha, Hu, Ji did too. Really thanks them.</p>

<p>But I did not cry, though I was sad, I was reluctant to leave the fellowship, the friends, the Bible Group &hellip;  When Dai asked me when I will be back to the fellowship. I answered maybe never. But Ji corrected me. He said we at last had one chance to see each other, we will see each other in the heaven. I said a wrong word. His correct is right.</p>

<p><code>Whatsoever thy hand findeth to do, do it with thy might; for there is no work, nor device, nor knowledge, nor wisdom, in the grave, whither thou goest.</code>    &mdash;Ecclesiastes 9:10</p>

<p>Do what you need to do.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_25_back-home.html">http://baham.co/06_25_back-home.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Church Meeting and Baptsim]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_22_church-meeting-and-baptsim.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-22T12:47:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/church-meeting-and-baptsim</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday is a Saturday, we attended church meeting. The teacher is from Taian, the subject is about Faith, Heresy, Her Witness and Fundamentals.</p>

<p>I was attracted with this. After I finished my procedures of graduation, I stayed in the church to listen the teaching.</p>

<p>And the teaching stoped at about 5:00 pm, then I went to be baptized.</p>

<p>This is a really rare chance to be baptized. Since I came to CUMT Fellowship, I found I was changed, and a few month ago, I found I wanted to be baptized. And this is the last chance to be baptized before graduation.</p>

<p>Really thanks God. Because he gave me this changce.</p>

<p>About baptsim. There are a lot of words in Bible.<!--more--></p>

<p><code>He that believeth and is baptized shall be saved; but he that believeth not shall be damned. --Mark 16:16</code></p>

<p><code>Therefore if any man be in Christ, he is a new creature: old things are passed away; behold, all things are become new. --Corinthians 5:17</code></p>

<p>And there is a witness about Philip and an eunuch.</p>

<p>The reason that I want to be baptized is only one, I want to be saved.</p>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_22_church-meeting-and-baptsim.html">http://baham.co/06_22_church-meeting-and-baptsim.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graduate]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_16_graduate.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-16T06:27:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/graduate</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday, brothers and sisters got together to learn God&rsquo;s words and say goodbye to graduates, like me.</p>

<p>I came to the fellowship in September 2013, and now I will leave.</p>

<p>And I find a difference between I came and I left, before I came to the fellowship, I had a heart made up of stone, but now I feel my heart is made up of flesh. What or who gave me this difference, I thing is God&rsquo;s words, it is Bible, it is Spirit.</p>

<p>I always thought I would not be sad when I graduate. But I find I am wrong, now. Because I feel sadness.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Before noon, Mrs Zhang call me to ask me about how to get water. And I just came to the fellowship.
I arrived at about 12:30, and there are many elders and classmates, I felt sleepy, cause I had a habit to sleep at noon.</p>

<p>I did not know how to say. So I just write it sorted by the time.</p>

<p>I bought steamed breads and condiments.</p>

<p>We sang songs to admire and praise God.</p>

<p>Pastor Lu gave us a lesson about how to keep the faith after graduatation in this guilty World.</p>

<p>A presentation of graduates, and I am the first, I did not prepare fot it.</p>

<p>Receiving the gifts and elders gave us a blessing and lesson(Pastor Yao and Aunt Diao and so on).</p>

<p>Cells&#8217; shows, and I paly a harmonica show and sang it  /simple gift/.</p>

<p>We lined in 2 circles and said goodbye.</p>

<p>We ate. There are really many people this time. Maybe 40-50 people.</p>

<p><code>I really don't know how to describe this day, what I can do is just write the title and keep the memory in my mind.</code></p>

<p>Thanks God!</p>

<p><code>And he answering said, Thou shalt love the Lord thy God with all thy heart, and with all thy soul, and with all thy strength, and with all thy mind; and thy neighbour as thyself.</code>  &mdash;Luke 10:27
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_16_graduate.html">http://baham.co/06_16_graduate.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix a harmonica tab's bugs]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_13_fix-a-harmonica-tabs-bugs.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-13T15:35:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/fix-a-harmonica-tabs-bugs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Skeeter&rsquo;s song <em>The end of the world</em> is a beautiful song. I want to play is with my harmonica. So I find id by startpage.</p>

<p>And there is a tab on harptabs.</p>

<p>It is a site to index a lot of harmonica tabs, and it is easy to use and kepp the <em>KISS</em> rule.</p>

<p>The tab is here<!--more--></p>

<p>The tab by <a href="https://www.harptabs.com/song.php?ID=2587">aussie</a></p>

<p>But this is something wrong with it.</p>

<p>So I find the bugs and fix them.</p>

<p>And submit a new <a href="https://www.harptabs.com/song.php?ID=21985">The end of the world harmonica tab</a></p>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_13_fix-a-harmonica-tabs-bugs.html">http://baham.co/06_13_fix-a-harmonica-tabs-bugs.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[google in china 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_10_google-in-china-2014.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-10T14:06:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/google-in-china-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These days, google is blocked by firewall in China.</p>

<p>You can not use gmail, access goagent, although this a new leader, but the range of block is more and more varient.</p>

<p>And now google is blocked.</p>

<h2>Resolve Google&rsquo;s Block in China<!--more--></h2>

<h3>ping the ip</h3>

<p><a href="http://www.super-ping.com">super ping</a></p>

<h3>use goagent</h3>

<p><a href="https://github.com/goagent/goagent">goagent</a></p>

<p>it is hosted on github, if you can not get it, try find host to github.</p>

<h2>The relevent articles in Chinese</h2>

<p>Chrome&rsquo;s quic:  <a href="http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3879.html">http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3879.html</a>
Find Google hosts: <a href="http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3878.html">http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3878.html</a>
google <a href="https:">https:</a> <a href="http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3872.html">http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3872.html</a>
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_10_google-in-china-2014.html">http://baham.co/06_10_google-in-china-2014.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rhinoceros in Love]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_09_rhinoceros-in-love.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-09T09:51:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/rhinoceros-in-love</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Every year, Stage Play Corporation in CUMT put a stage play. This year, my last year in University, the stage show is called &ldquo;Rhinoceros in Love&rdquo;, and the four years in university, I watched the stage show from this corporation 3 times, this is the third time. And  only this time I got a girl partener with me to watch it.</p>

<p>The first stage show I watched in CUMT is called &ldquo;暗恋桃花源&rdquo; in Chinese, the second was &ldquo;红玫瑰与白玫瑰&rdquo;, writed by Ailing Zhang, the title means &ldquo;Red Rose and White Rose&rdquo;. You know, all these three are about love.</p>

<p> This time getting a ticket of the stage show is more difficult than ever. There are 3 times to send the free tickets in the camp, I went twice but got nothing. So I gave up to watch the show, cause the third sending tickets was at Wen Chang Camp, I did not want to go so far to get the ticket.</p>

<p> But on Saturday, I had no intention of talking about the show with Ying at the fellowship when she finished cooking the dinner, she said she would do ask her friends as best as she can.
 <!--more-->
 At night back from fellowship, I send a message to Yan to remind her and asked her about my harmonica&rsquo;s show&rsquo;s time, after she sent back, I sent a message to ask about the show&rsquo;s ticket, cause I knew she do some students&#8217; job, and I knew maybe she had tickets.</p>

<p> She told me she want to watch too, but she did not get the ticket either. So I slept, cause tomorrow I wanted to join the praying in the morning. And shutdowned or airplaned my tcl and huawei phone.</p>

<p> I woke up about 6 am on Sunday, and I did not watch the phone.</p>

<p> On the road to the fellowship, I saw Ren, but he walked so fast that I could not get him, after I turned right out the sourth gate, I heard some steps, and I turn back, there is a girl, Yan. She told me maybe I did not receive the message she sent, I took out my phone from my pocket, I found she told me she get 2 tickets and invite me to watch the show with her.</p>

<p> <code>What a surprise God give me,  thanks God.</code></p>

<p> Before the time the show started, we get on the bus hiredby Materail College and we talked a lot on the road, about TV, driving exam, movies, novels and so on.</p>

<p> Even between the show, we still talked about the show, the plot of show, the music. The song from Skeeter Davis&mdash; &lsquo;the end of the world&rsquo; the song I really like.</p>

<p> On the back road, we still talked a lot, and she came with me to Xing 1 to get the onda pad, Cause I knew she did not get throuth the driving exam and I wanted to  lend her the pad to help her to get through the driving exam.</p>

<p> What a happy day and a meaningful experience, and thanks God to give me this happy experience and such beautiful friendship, such a kind friend.</p>

<p>And thanks  Yan&rsquo;s help. <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_09_rhinoceros-in-love.html">http://baham.co/06_09_rhinoceros-in-love.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What a Foolish Thing I made]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_07_what-a-foolish-thing-i-made.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-07T01:29:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/what-a-foolish-thing-i-made</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>  I talked at Hui&rsquo;s dormitory, Ning came to tell us Lei was fighted with others. And need someone to go to help him.</p>

<p>  After thinking this thing, I thought I would go with them.</p>

<p>  Then we went to Teachers&#8217; University. I did not the fighting thing&rsquo;s detail, but the aim I went is just to keep men calm down.</p>

<p>  But always thing you could not imageine happened.<!--more--></p>

<p>  Lijian is there, when we came, we went in the camp, and they just find the guy and kick him. I did not do this, cause I knew I came to make men calm. And Cheng/Cao/Hui either. What I thought is just that Lijian vent his anger on this. Then went back to school.</p>

<p>  After we left the camp, 4 men went on the TAXI, we others walked to wait other taxis, some guys run to catch us.</p>

<p>  2 were already on the taxi, and Cao said &lsquo;run&rsquo;. We run. We fime men run to a same direction.</p>

<p>  But they were on a taxi to catch us. What a fool, we went to the same direction. And I was caught up. Peng too. They asked me did I fight? I answerd no. Then to Peng, He said yes. And they took Peng. After the thinking, I left Peng and called others.</p>

<p>  Then we went back to Teachers&#8217; University, until we knew Peng is back. Finally, Peng is safe and sound.</p>

<p>  What a foolish thing I did, God will not like this, I did things by youth and without wisdom. THis is a lesson to me.</p>

<p>  And thanks God, keep me and anyothers from CUMT or from UT safe and sound.</p>

<p>  And when an unhappything happend, just please depend on God, and use your heart with love, and be patient.</p>

<pre><code>爱是恒久忍耐.
</code></pre>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_07_what-a-foolish-thing-i-made.html">http://baham.co/06_07_what-a-foolish-thing-i-made.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the block will end?]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_06_when-the-block-will-end.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-06T06:44:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/when-the-block-will-end</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These days, maybe started a one week ago, I can no access Google. Even replace the <em>hosts</em>, add<code>ncr</code>, I still can not access Google.</p>

<p>Must I use google as my search engineer? No, But I need to use digg to read my feed, use utb to watch some cool videos and these websites kind of need google&rsquo;s service.
And there is another bad thing<!--more--></p>

<p>Goagent can not be used either, A tool need google app engineer. And can be used as a proxy.</p>

<p>What the block in China will end? And why the gov hesitate its people? And why the gov lack of confidence?</p>

<p>Why?
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_06_when-the-block-will-end.html">http://baham.co/06_06_when-the-block-will-end.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Upgrade Linux mint16 to Linux mint 17 Qiana]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_01_upgrade-linux-mint16-to-linux-mint-17-qiana.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-01T00:48:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/upgrade-linux-mint16-to-linux-mint-17-qiana</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://www.linuxmint.com/pictures/screenshots/qiana/thumb_cinnamon.png" alt="mint 17" /></p>

<p>Linux mint 17 -Qiana released with Cinnamon or Mate Desktop Environment.</p>

<p>And I was using Min16 to write this article.</p>

<p>And the <code>dist-upgrade</code> is running.</p>

<p>But how to upgrade the linux mint to a newer version.</p>

<h2>1 Backup Your Files</h2>

<!--more-->


<p>This a very important step, although I did not back up my files. Cause I did not have a hardisk or webdrive with enough space.</p>

<p>And back your source like these:</p>

<pre><code>$ sudo cp /etc/apt/sources.list  /etc/apt/sources.list.bak
$ sudo cp /etc/apt/sources.list.d/official-package-repositories.list  /etc/apt/sources.list.d/official-package-repositories.list.bak
</code></pre>

<h2>2 Change your source</h2>

<p>Just replace <code>petra</code> with <code>qiana</code> and <code>saucy</code> with <code>trusty</code></p>

<h2>3 Upgrade</h2>

<pre><code>$ sudo apt-get update
$ sudo apt-get dist-upgrade
$ sudo apt-get upgrade
</code></pre>

<p>This is all.</p>

<p>And maybe you want to read this post too&mdash; <a href="http://www.tecmint.com/upgrade-linux-mint-16-to-linux-mint-17/">Upgrade Linux  mint</a>
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_01_upgrade-linux-mint16-to-linux-mint-17-qiana.html">http://baham.co/06_01_upgrade-linux-mint16-to-linux-mint-17-qiana.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Teach children to prevent sexual assault]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_30_teach-children-to-prevent-sexual-assault.html"/>
    <updated>2014-05-30T13:54:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/teach-children-to-prevent-sexual-assault</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Although I was not a parent, but I think this video from King of fairy tales Zheng Yuanjie is very meaningful.</p>

<p>Mr Zheng use Vampire and Pipilu to teach children to prevent sexual assault.</p>

<p>And the law he noticed is China&rsquo;s Law. But it is similar with other countries.</p>

<div><object id='sinaplayer' width='480' height='370' ><param name='allowScriptAccess' value='always' /><embed pluginspage='http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer' src='http://you.video.sina.com.cn/api/sinawebApi/outplayrefer.php/vid=130679715_478_1863229063_1_P0i0TXA/C2LK+l1lHz2stqlF+6xCpv2xhGu8vVGmJwdZUw+YJMXNb9wE4C/RCchD9HoLHcwydP0m0Rokb6td/s.swf' type='application/x-shockwave-flash' name='sinaplayer' allowFullScreen='true' allowScriptAccess='always' width='480' height='370'></embed></object></div>


<p>This is a video from <!--more-->
<a href="http://blog.sina.com.cn/s/blog_473abae60102dzyv.html">Zheng Yuanjie Blog</a></p>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/05_30_teach-children-to-prevent-sexual-assault.html">http://baham.co/05_30_teach-children-to-prevent-sexual-assault.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[one accosting]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_30_one-accosting.html"/>
    <updated>2014-05-30T13:03:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/one-accosting</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A long time ago. It is a month&rsquo;s tenth day. I do not remember the date.</p>

<p>I was on the train home. And a girl sat on the left of me.</p>

<p>A pretty girl with a slim legs and a white sports shoes. I think she is a college student too just like me.</p>

<p>But you know I am shy to talk to others especially a pretty girl.</p>

<p>Nearly at the midnight, I could not fall asleep. And I found she did not either.</p>

<p>And <!--more-->
I struggle a few times and started the accosting, maybe this is the first accosting in my life. And screwed up my courage to ask her &ldquo;Which stop she will take off the train?&rdquo;</p>

<p>Just write an article to remember this. Nothing else. I think this thing is worth to remember.</p>

<blockquote><p>_&lt;</p></blockquote>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/05_30_one-accosting.html">http://baham.co/05_30_one-accosting.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jesus knows Your pain]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_29_jesus-knows-your-pain.html"/>
    <updated>2014-05-29T08:02:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/jesus-knows-your-pain</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These 2 days, I just do one thing. It is writing my paper and instruction to the coal preparation plant I designed.</p>

<p>But this is one thing very bad , it is the college tell me to submit the instruction/paper/translation in may 29. But the noticed is opened at may 27.</p>

<p>And what I prayed to say Jesus is help me to give me strength and time to write the instuction. Cause I have not writen the instruction.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>And this notice made me unhappy.</p>

<p>Really unhappy.</p>

<p>But I gave this burden to Jesus, and search the help from Jesus.</p>

<p>I wake up at May 28, and I just write the words to the instruction.</p>

<p>I did not finished it by the night. And I slept at about 23 pm.</p>

<p>There is another thing make me unhappy. Cause I need to take physical examination at May 2y the same day as the submitting day.</p>

<p>These 2 days, I ate, I slept, I talked, I joined to Bible Study Group, But I was unhappy.</p>

<p>Until a little time later, I check my instruction and paper and so on with the check-paper too to verify whether my artcile had high repetition rate.</p>

<p>I got 10 percents. And the college&rsquo;s reqiurement is 20 percents.</p>

<p>Really thanks God.</p>

<pre><code>Hitherto have ye asked nothing in my name: ask, and ye shall receive, that your joy may be full.   --John 16;24
</code></pre>

<p>Jesus Really felt my pain and helped me. What love he gave!
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/05_29_jesus-knows-your-pain.html">http://baham.co/05_29_jesus-knows-your-pain.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ordination-The First Time I joined]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_23_ordination-the-first-time-i-joined.html"/>
    <updated>2014-05-23T01:12:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/ordination-the-first-time-i-joined</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> In May 21, the day of <code>521</code>, just like the word &lsquo;I love you&rsquo; in Chinese.</p>

<p> And in the morning, I went to Mineral Research Center to visit the Tan to check my drawing of the Coal Preparation Plant. And she and Mr Peng and others give a lot of advice and show some mistakes. So I need to take much time to redraw it.</p>

<p> And after noon. There is a report in college, I went to join it. Professor Zeng Hongbo make this report about some reseach in University of Alberta. He is less than 30,  but already was a professor.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>After te report, I found the time is 4 pm, and Miss Zhang send me a message about the Ordination. And I called Ma. She told me she will went back to dormitory firstly. And I think I need too. But when I came to the door of my dormitory, I found it is 4:20. We need to arrive North Gate before 4:40-50.</p>

<p>So I decided to buy a bottole of water and just go north. But Ma did not show.</p>

<p>And I sent a message to ask her where she is. She was in the dormitory and she tell me wait for her. Though I already was on the car to the North Gate, I off the car.</p>

<p>Some minutes later. She came, we went to the North and met Uncle Yao.</p>

<p>And we started to go to the XiXiang Church. It is a long distance. And we talked, talked about a lot of things. From now to a long time ago. Maybe when there 2 people who know each other with a long distance, they will talk a lot more than ever and shared their thought. And when we arrived Xi Xiang Church, It is about 6 pm.</p>

<p>And in Xi Xiang, I found we two have a job to hold the plate with presants.</p>

<p>Pator Ma Wenlong, a pator from US give me a talk about of heart and leadship of pator.</p>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/05_23_ordination-the-first-time-i-joined.html">http://baham.co/05_23_ordination-the-first-time-i-joined.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Tips to Writing More Beautiful Python Codes(For Beginners)]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_15_6-tips-to-writing-more-beautiful-python-codes.html"/>
    <updated>2014-05-15T06:12:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/6-tips-to-writing-more-beautiful-python-codes</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Python is an easy-learning programming language.  Its design philosophy emphasizes code readability. And if you did not know python, you can get the base knowledge on <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Python_%28programming_language%29">Wikipedia</a>.</p>

<h2>1 &ldquo;&rdquo;&ldquo;  use Three quotes</h2>

<p>In python 3 quotes is not just used to show <em>mutiline strings</em>, but also for <em>doc</em> in a function.</p>

<p>This will help users to understand this function.</p>

<p>Like: <!--more--></p>

<pre><code>def hw():
    """Output 'Hellow World'
    For example:
    &gt;&gt;&gt; hw()
    Hellow World!
    """
    print("Hellow World")
    return "Hellow World"
</code></pre>

<p>And the strings between 2 three quotes, not just commits but also an introduction for the function.</p>

<p>You can get the strings by <code>print(hw.__doc__)</code></p>

<pre><code>    Output 'Hellow World'
    For example:
    &gt;&gt;&gt; hw()
    Hellow World!
</code></pre>

<h2>2 Use Return    &mdash;functional programming</h2>

<p>Not every function need a <code>return</code>(just like the function <code>greet()</code>below the title &lsquo;use keywords as default parameter&rsquo;), if you do not type a <code>return</code>, python consider you typed a <code>return None</code>.</p>

<p>But if you like <code>functional programming</code>, like <em>Scale</em>, <em>R</em> and so on. You need add <code>return</code> in every function.</p>

<h3>2.1functional programming</h3>

<pre><code>There are not variables or side effect, you can only edit things by the `return`.
</code></pre>

<h2>3 Use <code>main()</code></h2>

<p>You know <code>main</code> is not necessary. Using <code>main()</code>is just an agreement.</p>

<p>Just make python&rsquo;s code more comfortable for who have learned Java or C++.</p>

<h2>4 Use keywords as default parameter</h2>

<ol>
<li>It will show the parameter&rsquo;s value directly;</li>
<li>The order of the parameter with keywords doesn&rsquo;t matter.</li>
</ol>


<p>Just like this:</p>

<pre><code>def greet(name='Bob', greeting='Hellow'):
    print(greeting, name+'!')
</code></pre>

<h2>5 Import Package name like <code>import packagename</code></h2>

<p>Cause when you import package like: <code>from packagename import *</code></p>

<p>When there is a same name in your own code with in the packege, it will overwrite it.</p>

<p>So use <code>import packagename</code> insted of using <code>from packagename import *</code>.</p>

<p>And use <code>packagename.functionname</code> to use the function.</p>

<h2>6 Using negative number for an index</h2>

<pre><code>a   p   p   l   e
0   1   2   3   4
-5  -4  -3  -2  -1
</code></pre>

<p>Maybe it will take more time to find the exact the negative index. But it will avoid some mistakes when you operate an array or string with <code>delete</code>. <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/05_15_6-tips-to-writing-more-beautiful-python-codes.html">http://baham.co/05_15_6-tips-to-writing-more-beautiful-python-codes.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[About the Translation Category]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_14_about-the-translation-category.html"/>
    <updated>2014-05-14T06:02:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/about-the-translation-category</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After I move the language on this site from Chinese to English.</p>

<p>I decide to make a subpage or subdomian to include some Chinese translations from English.</p>

<p>And the translation articles mouved to <a href="http://translation.baham.co">baham&rsquo;s translation</a></p>

<!--more-->


<p>And this category <a href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/translation/">translation</a> maybe will include some articles translated from Chinese.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/05_14_about-the-translation-category.html">http://baham.co/05_14_about-the-translation-category.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
