<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2014-08-04T14:03:03+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Using the Kobo Glo]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/08_04_using-the-kobo-glo.html"/>
    <updated>2014-08-04T13:44:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/using-the-kobo-glo</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I wanted to buy an elink ereader long long ago. But I did not buy it, cause I did not have enough money.</p>

<p>After I got my first week salary, I wanted to buy something for myself. I find my roomate Ning has a Kindle 3 ereader. I try to use it, it is pretty cool. And I find it has a enough good reading experienment, though it is an old version of Kindle. You know my salary is not enough to buy a Kindle Paperwhite. When I saw this ereaker, I decided not to buy kpw. After the contrasting with different ereaders, Kindle, kobo, nook. Finally, I decided to buy kobo glo.<!--more--></p>

<ol>
<li>I need a erader with backlit;</li>
<li>The price  less than 650 yuan;</li>
<li>Just an ereader, not an android device;</li>
<li>Bigger screen resolution.</li>
</ol>


<p>So what I contrast are kpw1, kpw2, nook3, nook4, kobo glo. The kobo glo is my last choice.</p>

<p>When you started to use it, you must need a wifi to connect kobo server to update or to buy books. And there are 2 interesting things, &lsquo;Reading Stats and Rewards&rsquo;, very cool tools.</p>

<p>When I thingking how to use this salary, originally, I wanted to but a bike. So I can rike it to church or travel. But Biao advise me to buy a more expensive one,&lsquo;Battle&rsquo;, so I delay buying a bike. But I still will buy one in one day.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/08_04_using-the-kobo-glo.html">http://baham.co/08_04_using-the-kobo-glo.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I built a Flotation Separator with blender]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/08_01_i-built-a-floation-separator-with-blender.html"/>
    <updated>2014-08-01T00:58:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/i-built-a-floation-separator-with-blender</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://baham.co/images/mineral/flotation1.jpg" alt="Flotation Separator" />
Boss Xie had talked with us fresh men about the 3D moduling, he thought the studio need men to build 3D module. And I can kind of use <em>Blender</em>, I told him this.</p>

<p>After this talk, I started learning and using blender again. Though I had no books to watch. But there are many tutorials in my disk, after all, blender is an open software. A few days ago, I finished this flotation separator.<!--more--></p>

<p><img src="http://baham.co/images/mineral/flotation2.jpg" alt="FS" /></p>

<p>It is not very cool, or verisimilitude. But at least, when I show this to Biao, he can recognize it.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/08_01_i-built-a-floation-separator-with-blender.html">http://baham.co/08_01_i-built-a-floation-separator-with-blender.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Churches I met in Dandong]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_31_3-churches-i-met-in-dandong.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-31T08:40:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/3-churches-i-met-in-dandong</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I find church after I came to Dandong. I found a Church in Jvhuashan on the map, but I found it is Sabbath Sect. And I remebered at the last church meeting in CUMT, Duan told us Sabbath Sect is heresy.</p>

<p>But on the road back to the company, I found a plate&mdash;God love the world. And that day is a Thursday, there is a bible study group on Thursday there. So I went there at night.<!--more--></p>

<p>And I posted a post on tieba of LDXY. I asked about if there is fellowship there. Jin told me yes, and gave me qq group ID. I joined it, and after I came back from Wulongbei, On Sunday, I went there with Yan.</p>

<p>And before I left, Aunty Meng told me coming here to church meeting and not going to three self principle church.</p>

<p>But some days later, after I ran back. I met a brother, he is from the Church near  Yuanbaoshan, a 3-self principle church, he told me do not go to underground/family church.</p>

<p>In fact, I prefer to going to family church, cause there are small number of people,  but I went to 3-self principle church too, like at my hometown or in Pingdingshan.</p>

<p>I still remembered Ji&rsquo;s share after he back from Australia, he said, in Australia, different religious sects will sent the posts together, when they have the same centra truth. Does a person be saved depends on family church or 3-self principle church he went to. No, I do not think so.</p>

<p><code>For it is by grace you have been saved, through faith-and this not from yourselves, it is the gift of God--</code> &mdash;Ephesians 2:8
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_31_3-churches-i-met-in-dandong.html">http://baham.co/07_31_3-churches-i-met-in-dandong.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The difference between Coal Preparation and the Metal Preparation]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_25_the-difference-between-coal-preparation-and-the-metal-preparation.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-25T12:51:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-difference-between-coal-preparation-and-the-metal-preparation</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Most of what I learned in university is coal processing, though my major is called mineral processing. And trully, I just learned fewer knowledge about other mineral&rsquo;s processing than coal. But the company&rsquo;s business is more relative about metal. And there was mineral processing training these days. It is about mineral, especially metal. After the company&rsquo;s train and learning in school, I want to talk about the things about the difference between coal and metal. And I want to tell you directly,
<em>There is no difference originally.</em></p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Some teachers&#8217; mislead</h2>

<p>Neally all teachers in CUMT tell us most of the CUMT&rsquo;s courses are about coal. Though there are courses about non-metal minerals, iron and smelting, though some teachers disagree.</p>

<p>But they ignore one thing, the methods to prepare minerals is the same.</p>

<h2>There is only one teaching material about Mineral Processing in China</h2>

<p>Not only the method is the same, but the teaching material. I found the students from NEU, CUMTB, HPU who learn Mineral Processing were all using the same book <em>Mineral Processing</em> edited in chage by Xie Guangyuan. Who is the dean of my college.</p>

<h2>The same mechines are used in metal and coal</h2>

<p>Jinjing, Haiwang, Derick the same companies are chosen to choose the mechines during directing plant. In old time, I think there is a lot of difference between designing a mineral praparation plant and a coal preparation plant. After the train, I found it is not, most of the companies&#8217; mechines are for coal or metal or other minerals.</p>

<p>In other words, I hope the graduate from CUMT remember our school&rsquo;s name is CUMT not China&rsquo;s University of Coal and Technology. And I hope the social, the non-coal preparation plant trust graduate from CUMT. We can not only prepare coal but also metal, non-coal.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_25_the-difference-between-coal-preparation-and-the-metal-preparation.html">http://baham.co/07_25_the-difference-between-coal-preparation-and-the-metal-preparation.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First Week's Salary]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_25_the-first-weeks-salary.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-25T12:43:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-first-weeks-salary</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A few days ago, I got my firsk week&rsquo;s salary. It is not too much, just a few hundred yuan.<!--more--> But it is really meaningful.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_25_the-first-weeks-salary.html">http://baham.co/07_25_the-first-weeks-salary.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven Days' Train]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_17_seven-days-train.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-17T09:19:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/seven-days-train</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I did not worked in 7 Days Hotel, not lived in &lsquo;7 Days&rsquo; either.</p>

<p>Because the company prepare 7 days to train us, freshmen.</p>

<p>What we do between the train, is learning and knowing each other.</p>

<p>And you know, I am not very good at making friends, or remember new guys. So, in the first several days, I did not do well at knowing each other. But in the last several days, when we knew more about each other, our relashionship is more close.<!--more--></p>

<p>Most of time, I did not drink to avoid being drunk, this time, I drink some beer. When you drink, you want to talk, so I talked more than ever, but I still have clear mind to control my mouth.</p>

<p><code>Let us walk honestly, as in the day; not in rioting and drunkenness, not in chambering and wantonness, not in strife and envying. </code>  &mdash;Romans 13:13</p>

<p>And between the 7 days train, there are 2 teachers/ministers&#8217; talk I can not forget. One is the minister of planning department &mdash; Mr Wang, the other is the vice general manager &mdash;Mr Fan.</p>

<p>Wang talked one book&mdash;<em>Secret</em>, the book belongs to New Age Movement. Before I left CUMT, at the last church meeting,  Duan taught us how to distinguish heresy. And she remind us of the New Age Movement and the book <em>Secret</em>.  Maybe Mr Wang is member of the Party, maybe he is not. But what he talked really did not suit the communism, or athesim, and did not suit the Christianity either. And I really want to talk about the religion with him, make him know Jesus.</p>

<p>As Mr Fan, he is smart. He talked a lot. About value of man, about wealth, about work, his experience and so on. And one thing he talked make me remember him. He said &ldquo;Men need Belief, professing a belief in Christianity is more than without belief.&rdquo; And as this word, I do not know wether he has join the Church meeting, and I did not know how to reply, or how to explain the difference of  the belief he said and the belief beliver profess in. So I said nothing, and just listened.</p>

<p>And Fan said men shouldn&rsquo;t attach great importance to wealth, I agrre with him about this, though I am not wealthy. But, after his word, some one express different opinion, said his opinion is all by he is already wealthy.</p>

<p>Men need belief, China needs belief. But communism is not a belief, money is not either. <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_17_seven-days-train.html">http://baham.co/07_17_seven-days-train.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Muslim Girl I Know]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_15_a-muslim-girl-i-know.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-15T05:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/a-muslim-girl-i-know</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There is a Muslim girl in company. I kind of knew her, but she did not. Because when we were still at school to find jobs. I saw her a lot of times in application meeting. And sometimes she introduce herself, I was still at the meeting. And got some information about her. Of cause, I did not do this by purpose. Maybe she did not remember me. But I remembered her. Because she is a Muslim and a Hui nationality girl, and has a boyfriend who is Han nationality, and she had joined one and only one students organization &mdash;Stage Show Organization. And you know I am fan of CUMT Stage Show.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I did not knew her came to the same compony as me until I found her name in the QQ group. And I had talked to her about why came here so far away from her home, she replied me she got this offer firstly.</p>

<p>In one application meeting, I found her is in too. And the HR asked her about her religion and what she is different form Han nationality girl. I generally remember she replied although she is a Hui nationality girl, but after she came to the university, she eat with classmates who are not Muslim, and she has a boyfriend who is a Han nantionality boy.</p>

<p>Though the HR did not say his opinion, did not say why he did not accept her. But that time I felt the HR rejudice her. Not rejudice her grades, or her appearance or her ability. He rejudice her religion. He worried the difference between Han and Hui will make some mistake in the fulture in the compony, though she said she already adopt Han&rsquo;s traditions and habits. The HR&rsquo;s worry is not gone.</p>

<p>Why I write this and why I remeber this, because one day when we ate in the same desktop. I found when she ate, she just eat a few kinds of dishes(without pork). Maybe when she came dfmc&rsquo;s application meeting, she did not emphasize her religion. And the company did not prepare the Islamic food for her. And when I saw this, I really really symphathize her. And I really want to tell her what you eat or waht you did not eat can not make you be saved, or make you be liked by God.</p>

<p>I wanted to, but I really do not know how to, and dare not to. I am a Christian, when I introduce myself, I will tell the listeners, including her, a Muslim. And she is a Muslim, she did not emphasize this. But when she sat before the desktop, I really can not understand her feeling or her thoughts about the food with pork.</p>

<p>I want to help her, not because she is a classmate of mine, not because she is a pretty girl, just because I want to, and not only  her, but also the Koren over the river, and the men who did not believe the God&hellip;&hellip;</p>

<p>May God bless.</p>

<p><code>For God so loved the world, that he gave his only begotten Son, that whosoever believeth in him should not perish, but have everlasting life.</code>  &mdash;John3:16 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_15_a-muslim-girl-i-know.html">http://baham.co/07_15_a-muslim-girl-i-know.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Driving]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_10_driving.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-10T08:47:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/driving</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>After I get the driving license, I neally ever drive.</p>

<p>But there is a chance for me to drive.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The day befor I take the Toefl Test, my siste and my brother in law came to join the wedding.</p>

<p>Although the driver, my brother in law try to avoid dringking, but it failed. And he need to work tomorrow, and my sister too.</p>

<p>So the driving burden came to me, I did not the lenth from my home to my sister and brother in law&rsquo;s apartment, but maybe 30 kilometers or more.</p>

<p>This is my first time to drive so far after I get the driving license.</p>

<p>Just write this article to remember this thing.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_10_driving.html">http://baham.co/07_10_driving.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toefl Test I Took.]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_10_toefl-test-i-took.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-10T08:02:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/toefl-test-i-took</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my first time to take Toefl Test. After I graduated and left the camp. I prepared for the toefl test. But I didn&rsquo;t prepared it well. I even not finished the one whole office guide test. It is really a pity. Wahtever, the porpose I take it is just verified my English skill, although the scores did not public, but the I achive the porpose, my English-skill is bad.</p>

<p>What I need do is learning and practicing.</p>

<p>The 4 parts in toefl, I nearlly did not finished one of them well.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>In Reading Section, After I finished the first one, I found I did not have enought time . And I feel nervous, and you know, many answers are guessed by me.</p>

<p>And the listening section, what I pay the muchest time to practice, but what I can understand is just a little. And I was too tired to concentrate on the convesations or lecture. This is a lesson, when you take the test, you must sleep well and enough.</p>

<p>Then it is speaking, I found I can not read the paragraphes on time. As for the questions about speaking by oneself, I could not prepare them well in 15 seconds. I need to practice thinking in the heart with English.</p>

<p>What is the last is Writing Section. Maybe it will gave me the best score in 4 parts. But you know, they are still not good articles, it&rsquo;s just like an articles that writen by a pupil. not like an article by a high school graduation.</p>

<p>What I need to practice and learn is very much.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_10_toefl-test-i-took.html">http://baham.co/07_10_toefl-test-i-took.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Train to the Dandong]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_08_the-train-to-the-dandong.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-08T01:55:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-train-to-the-dandong</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> I bought a train ticket from Heb to Dandng, though I can not get on the car in Heb City. Because I found I can buy a sleeper ticket from Heb, not from my hometown. So I bought this ticket.</p>

<p>A few days later, when I went to get the ticket, I found I mmade a mistake, the ticket I bought is a student ticket. But you know I am not a student anymore. So the functionary asked me for the student card, I could not gave it. So what I can do is getting a refund for the ticket. And buy a chair ticket from my hometown. What the puzzle I will face with is I need sit on a chair more than 9 hours during the night. It will make me tired.</p>

<p>Before I leaving home, I pray to God for my travel, my safety  and my job.</p>

<p>I arrived at railway station about 6 pm, but the arrving in the raiway&rsquo;s time is about 5 hours later. So I went to Wanda Cinema to watch <em>Transform 4</em>. Though the ticket is expensive.<!--more--></p>

<p>This is my first time to watch <em>Transform</em>.</p>

<p>When the time is up, I went to the station to get on the railway. When I was on the railway, I found the functionary said there is an opportunity to buy a sleeper ticket. So I queue, although there is someone jumping the queue, There is an amazing thing happen, I bought the sleeper ticket, the last one.</p>

<p>When I get the sleeper ticket, I went to the sleeper car. I through many sleeper cays. Some has a very bad smell from someone&rsquo;s feet. I said in my heart I do not want to meet the one with bad feet smell. Finally, it did. But I found another bad thing, someone near me  snored with a very big noise. I could not wake him up, we did not know each other. What I can do is praying, like Hu said his experience with his roommate, I pray for my sleep time. It worked, subway started, I fell in a sleep until the nexr day&rsquo;s morning.</p>

<p>And there was another thing happen, when I queue to buy the sleeper ticket, I bought the last one, The functionary said, I got an amazing phone number and the ID number and the ticket number. And you know I bought the last sleeper ticket.</p>

<p>Am I lucky?</p>

<p>No! It is all on God&rsquo;s blessing.</p>

<p>Because there is a word in Holy Bible&mdash;</p>

<p><code>Hitherto have ye asked nothing in my name: ask, and ye shall receive, that your joy may be full.  </code>  &mdash; John 16:1
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_08_the-train-to-the-dandong.html">http://baham.co/07_08_the-train-to-the-dandong.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smartphone]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_01_smart-phone.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-01T08:59:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/smart-phone</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>My old android phone is broken, it can not start up. I did not know why? Because when I pluged in its battery on the night. It still could work. But when I wake up, it could not start up.</p>

<p>So I just found out my old Windows Mobile phone, my first smart phone with 64Mhz cpu and 64M ram, but it rum more smoothly than most cheap android phones.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>But there is a problwem when I use the wm phone, cause it can not get a normal signal. The intensity it get is alwasy weak. So I need a new phone. Though I want to buy a new phone after I started to work originally.</p>

<p>The Nokia X is my first choice, because of Nokia&rsquo;s fame. But most of markets did not sell it. So I bought a samsung android phone. And it is cheaper than nokia x. Cause I just need an android smart phone which can run smoothly. This samsung phone is enough for me. And I can not afford an expensive phone. So I choose it.</p>

<p>Android, Firefox OS, Ubuntu Phone, Tizen &hellip; there are more and more phone os now. But the os I like mostly is wm.</p>

<p>Smooth, Light, though ms would not support it. Writing this article is to remember the OSes, and the smartphones I used.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/07_01_smart-phone.html">http://baham.co/07_01_smart-phone.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Time To Read All Contents of Bible]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_25_first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-25T12:50:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tonight, I read the <em>Malachi</em>, the last one in Old Testament.</p>

<p>Since September 2013, I started to read Bible. And I finshed reading all content of Holy Bible.</p>

<p>Write this post to remember this day.</p>

<!--more-->


<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_25_first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible.html">http://baham.co/06_25_first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[back home]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_25_back-home.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-25T07:32:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/back-home</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The school ask us to leave by 6.23, I left at June 23. I wanted to leave at 21. But I change the plan to decide to leave at 6.23.</p>

<p>I took the railway and the taxi to home.</p>

<p>There are cleaner air in hometown than Xuzhou or other cities I had visited in China.</p>

<p>But you know the time to work is coming. So there is not much time for me to stay in hometown. And I still had a Toefl test to take.</p>

<h2>Guy from South China on Railway</h2>

<!--more-->


<p>When the railway is arriving My Province, the guy in a lower berth spoke something to another one. And I talked to him about trifles.</p>

<p>After the talk, I found goal is near my home. But the difference is that I need take a taxi, but he wanted to ride a bike to the destination. He graduate from Guangdong and worked in Nanjing before coming here.</p>

<h2>Girls near my berth</h2>

<p>There are 6 berthes right of my berth. After arriving my destination  I found there are 3 girls who knew each other, and 2 girls who knew each other, and 1 elder women who is not like a student. You know that 3 girls always talked. And I just listen, they talked boyfriend, wealth, life and so on. And you know it is a time to listen, to listen girls&#8217; thoughts and feelings.</p>

<h2>Family left of my berth.</h2>

<p>On the left of my berth, there is one family, one daughter, one father, and one mother. The daughter is just like me, graduated from college and went back home. They live in Liaoning Province. The daughter studied in Nanjing. And theis pronunciation is kind of like Ma.</p>

<h2>Summary</h2>

<p>This travel maybe is the my last travel from Xuzhou. My students who still in Xuzhou they saw me off, and Sha, Hu, Ji did too. Really thanks them.</p>

<p>But I did not cry, though I was sad, I was reluctant to leave the fellowship, the friends, the Bible Group &hellip;  When Dai asked me when I will be back to the fellowship. I answered maybe never. But Ji corrected me. He said we at last had one chance to see each other, we will see each other in the heaven. I said a wrong word. His correct is right.</p>

<p><code>Whatsoever thy hand findeth to do, do it with thy might; for there is no work, nor device, nor knowledge, nor wisdom, in the grave, whither thou goest.</code>    &mdash;Ecclesiastes 9:10</p>

<p>Do what you need to do.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_25_back-home.html">http://baham.co/06_25_back-home.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Church Meeting and Baptsim]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_22_church-meeting-and-baptsim.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-22T12:47:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/church-meeting-and-baptsim</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday is a Saturday, we attended church meeting. The teacher is from Taian, the subject is about Faith, Heresy, Her Witness and Fundamentals.</p>

<p>I was attracted with this. After I finished my procedures of graduation, I stayed in the church to listen the teaching.</p>

<p>And the teaching stoped at about 5:00 pm, then I went to be baptized.</p>

<p>This is a really rare chance to be baptized. Since I came to CUMT Fellowship, I found I was changed, and a few month ago, I found I wanted to be baptized. And this is the last chance to be baptized before graduation.</p>

<p>Really thanks God. Because he gave me this changce.</p>

<p>About baptsim. There are a lot of words in Bible.<!--more--></p>

<p><code>He that believeth and is baptized shall be saved; but he that believeth not shall be damned. --Mark 16:16</code></p>

<p><code>Therefore if any man be in Christ, he is a new creature: old things are passed away; behold, all things are become new. --Corinthians 5:17</code></p>

<p>And there is a witness about Philip and an eunuch.</p>

<p>The reason that I want to be baptized is only one, I want to be saved.</p>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_22_church-meeting-and-baptsim.html">http://baham.co/06_22_church-meeting-and-baptsim.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graduate]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_16_graduate.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-16T06:27:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/graduate</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday, brothers and sisters got together to learn God&rsquo;s words and say goodbye to graduates, like me.</p>

<p>I came to the fellowship in September 2013, and now I will leave.</p>

<p>And I find a difference between I came and I left, before I came to the fellowship, I had a heart made up of stone, but now I feel my heart is made up of flesh. What or who gave me this difference, I thing is God&rsquo;s words, it is Bible, it is Spirit.</p>

<p>I always thought I would not be sad when I graduate. But I find I am wrong, now. Because I feel sadness.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Before noon, Mrs Zhang call me to ask me about how to get water. And I just came to the fellowship.
I arrived at about 12:30, and there are many elders and classmates, I felt sleepy, cause I had a habit to sleep at noon.</p>

<p>I did not know how to say. So I just write it sorted by the time.</p>

<p>I bought steamed breads and condiments.</p>

<p>We sang songs to admire and praise God.</p>

<p>Pastor Lu gave us a lesson about how to keep the faith after graduatation in this guilty World.</p>

<p>A presentation of graduates, and I am the first, I did not prepare fot it.</p>

<p>Receiving the gifts and elders gave us a blessing and lesson(Pastor Yao and Aunt Diao and so on).</p>

<p>Cells&#8217; shows, and I paly a harmonica show and sang it  /simple gift/.</p>

<p>We lined in 2 circles and said goodbye.</p>

<p>We ate. There are really many people this time. Maybe 40-50 people.</p>

<p><code>I really don't know how to describe this day, what I can do is just write the title and keep the memory in my mind.</code></p>

<p>Thanks God!</p>

<p><code>And he answering said, Thou shalt love the Lord thy God with all thy heart, and with all thy soul, and with all thy strength, and with all thy mind; and thy neighbour as thyself.</code>  &mdash;Luke 10:27
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_16_graduate.html">http://baham.co/06_16_graduate.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fix a harmonica tab's bugs]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_13_fix-a-harmonica-tabs-bugs.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-13T15:35:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/fix-a-harmonica-tabs-bugs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Skeeter&rsquo;s song <em>The end of the world</em> is a beautiful song. I want to play is with my harmonica. So I find id by startpage.</p>

<p>And there is a tab on harptabs.</p>

<p>It is a site to index a lot of harmonica tabs, and it is easy to use and kepp the <em>KISS</em> rule.</p>

<p>The tab is here<!--more--></p>

<p>The tab by <a href="https://www.harptabs.com/song.php?ID=2587">aussie</a></p>

<p>But this is something wrong with it.</p>

<p>So I find the bugs and fix them.</p>

<p>And submit a new <a href="https://www.harptabs.com/song.php?ID=21985">The end of the world harmonica tab</a></p>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_13_fix-a-harmonica-tabs-bugs.html">http://baham.co/06_13_fix-a-harmonica-tabs-bugs.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[google in china 2014]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_10_google-in-china-2014.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-10T14:06:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/google-in-china-2014</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These days, google is blocked by firewall in China.</p>

<p>You can not use gmail, access goagent, although this a new leader, but the range of block is more and more varient.</p>

<p>And now google is blocked.</p>

<h2>Resolve Google&rsquo;s Block in China<!--more--></h2>

<h3>ping the ip</h3>

<p><a href="http://www.super-ping.com">super ping</a></p>

<h3>use goagent</h3>

<p><a href="https://github.com/goagent/goagent">goagent</a></p>

<p>it is hosted on github, if you can not get it, try find host to github.</p>

<h2>The relevent articles in Chinese</h2>

<p>Chrome&rsquo;s quic:  <a href="http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3879.html">http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3879.html</a>
Find Google hosts: <a href="http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3878.html">http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3878.html</a>
google <a href="https:">https:</a> <a href="http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3872.html">http://www.williamlong.info/archives/3872.html</a>
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_10_google-in-china-2014.html">http://baham.co/06_10_google-in-china-2014.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rhinoceros in Love]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_09_rhinoceros-in-love.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-09T09:51:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/rhinoceros-in-love</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Every year, Stage Play Corporation in CUMT put a stage play. This year, my last year in University, the stage show is called &ldquo;Rhinoceros in Love&rdquo;, and the four years in university, I watched the stage show from this corporation 3 times, this is the third time.</p>

<p>The first stage show I watched in CUMT is called &ldquo;暗恋桃花源&rdquo; in Chinese, the second was &ldquo;红玫瑰与白玫瑰&rdquo;, writed by Ailing Zhang, the title means &ldquo;Red Rose and White Rose&rdquo;. You know, all these three are about love.</p>

<p> This time getting a ticket of the stage show is more difficult than ever. There are 3 times to send the free tickets in the camp, I went twice but got nothing. So I gave up to watch the show, cause the third sending tickets was at Wen Chang Camp, I did not want to go so far to get the ticket.</p>

<p> But on Saturday, I had no intention of talking about the show with Ying at the fellowship when she finished cooking the dinner, she said she would do ask her friends as best as she can.
 <!--more-->
 At night back from fellowship, I send a message to Yan to remind her and asked her about my harmonica&rsquo;s show&rsquo;s time, after she sent back, I sent a message to ask about the show&rsquo;s ticket, cause I knew she do some students&#8217; job, and I knew maybe she had tickets.</p>

<p> She told me she want to watch too, but she did not get the ticket either. So I slept, cause tomorrow I wanted to join the praying in the morning. And shutdowned or airplaned my tcl and huawei phone.</p>

<p> I woke up about 6 am on Sunday, and I did not watch the phone.</p>

<p> On the road to the fellowship, I saw Ren, but he walked so fast that I could not get him, after I turned right out the sourth gate, I heard some steps, and I turn back, there is a girl, Yan. She told me maybe I did not receive the message she sent, I took out my phone from my pocket, I found she told me she get 2 tickets and invite me to watch the show.</p>

<p> <code>What a surprise.</code></p>

<p> Before the time the show started, we get on the bus hired by Materail College and we talked a lot on the road, about TV, driving exam, movies, novels and so on. And she tell me the captain teacher, that who really like the show, the art and literature.</p>

<p> When we arrived in Wenchang Camp, the theatre is neally full filled. And there are many my classmates, Jin, Ren, Jiao, Wu and so on.</p>

<p> In the show, there is an interlude, the song from Skeeter Davis&mdash; &lsquo;the end of the world&rsquo;, the song I really like, (And this song is used in Hanhan’s film &mdash; <em>Hou Hui Wu Qi</em>, It means ‘never meet again’. And it is used in ‘Under the Doom’ too. )</p>

<p> When we got back to the Nanhu Camp, I lent my onda pad for Yan, Cause I found she did not get throuth the driving exam and had a android pad not used for a long time, though that time I found my pad’s battery is empty, and the app was uninstalled.</p>

<p> What a happy day and a meaningful experience, and thanks God to give me this happy experience and such beautiful friendship.</p>

<p>And thanks  Yan&rsquo;s help. <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_09_rhinoceros-in-love.html">http://baham.co/06_09_rhinoceros-in-love.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What a Foolish Thing I made]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_07_what-a-foolish-thing-i-made.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-07T01:29:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/what-a-foolish-thing-i-made</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>  I talked at Hui&rsquo;s dormitory, Ning came to tell us Lei was fighted with others. And need someone to go to help him.</p>

<p>  After thinking this thing, I thought I would go with them.</p>

<p>  Then we went to Teachers&#8217; University. I did not the fighting thing&rsquo;s detail, but the aim I went is just to keep men calm down.</p>

<p>  But always thing you could not imageine happened.<!--more--></p>

<p>  Lijian is there, when we came, we went in the camp, and they just find the guy and kick him. I did not do this, cause I knew I came to make men calm. And Cheng/Cao/Hui either. What I thought is just that Lijian vent his anger on this. Then went back to school.</p>

<p>  After we left the camp, 4 men went on the TAXI, we others walked to wait other taxis, some guys run to catch us.</p>

<p>  2 were already on the taxi, and Cao said &lsquo;run&rsquo;. We run. We fime men run to a same direction.</p>

<p>  But they were on a taxi to catch us. What a fool, we went to the same direction. And I was caught up. Peng too. They asked me did I fight? I answerd no. Then to Peng, He said yes. And they took Peng. After the thinking, I left Peng and called others.</p>

<p>  Then we went back to Teachers&#8217; University, until we knew Peng is back. Finally, Peng is safe and sound.</p>

<p>  What a foolish thing I did, God will not like this, I did things by youth and without wisdom. THis is a lesson to me.</p>

<p>  And thanks God, keep me and anyothers from CUMT or from UT safe and sound.</p>

<p>  And when an unhappything happend, just please depend on God, and use your heart with love, and be patient.</p>

<pre><code>爱是恒久忍耐.
</code></pre>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_07_what-a-foolish-thing-i-made.html">http://baham.co/06_07_what-a-foolish-thing-i-made.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[When the block will end?]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_06_when-the-block-will-end.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-06T06:44:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/when-the-block-will-end</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These days, maybe started a one week ago, I can no access Google. Even replace the <em>hosts</em>, add<code>ncr</code>, I still can not access Google.</p>

<p>Must I use google as my search engineer? No, But I need to use digg to read my feed, use utb to watch some cool videos and these websites kind of need google&rsquo;s service.
And there is another bad thing<!--more--></p>

<p>Goagent can not be used either, A tool need google app engineer. And can be used as a proxy.</p>

<p>What the block in China will end? And why the gov hesitate its people? And why the gov lack of confidence?</p>

<p>Why?
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/06_06_when-the-block-will-end.html">http://baham.co/06_06_when-the-block-will-end.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
