<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2015-05-13T06:08:20+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octopree plugin popular post]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_11_a.html"/>
    <updated>2015-05-11T12:54:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/a</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I just generate my site. But it just generated nothing without errors noticing.
I did not find anything about it online.
Finally, I solve it.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Just delete the <em>popular post plugin</em>.
Because this plugin will find the value of google pr, but Chinese can not visit google.
So this process of generation is paused.</p>

<p>This plugin&rsquo;s location:</p>

<pre><code>plugins/popular_post.rb
</code></pre>

<h3>PS:</h3>

<p>And do not use popular side.</p>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/05_11_a.html">http://baham.co/05_11_a.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Domain On Sale]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/04_07_domain-on-sale.html"/>
    <updated>2015-04-07T12:56:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/domain-on-sale</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Last post is months ago. And after I graduated and worked, I have less time to keep my blog updating immediately.</p>

<p>So I decide to sell my domain.</p>

<p>And contents of blog is not on sale. So every visitors can visit the <a href="http://baham.github.io">baham</a> to get the old posts and pages.</p>

<p>After all, octopress was updated to vesion 3. I and my site call for changes too.</p>

<p>More information is at <a href="http://baham.co/sale">domain on sale</a></p>

<!--more-->


<p>And ocasionally, I found some blogs link to my posts. It is very meaningful for me. For this said this blog I kept for nearlly 3 year is helpful for someone. This is enough.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/04_07_domain-on-sale.html">http://baham.co/04_07_domain-on-sale.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dogs and The Smile]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_27_the-dogs-and-the-smile.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-27T10:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-dogs-and-the-smile</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> On the noon, when I had my lunch, I still take the rest food of mine to feed the dogs, that I found about month ago.</p>

<p> Days earlier, still on the noon. When I went dowstairs, there was still a woman there fo feed the dogs with milk. And I got some information about the dogs from her.</p>

<p> The mom dod bore the child dogs here, and it is a homeless dog. So now the three are all homeless.</p>

<p> And for me, I found the mom dog in a night when I debug my bicycle. In that time, I still do not know its nest, neither not its child dogs.</p>

<p>But today noon, <!--more-->
When I fed them. The mom dog did not bark to me. This the fourth day since I take them food.</p>

<p>And I smile, and felt happy. Really happy! When I saw it the scene.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/11_27_the-dogs-and-the-smile.html">http://baham.co/11_27_the-dogs-and-the-smile.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Cross]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_23_the-cross.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-23T05:01:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-cross</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I bought a silver cross from taobao, at Novermber 11.</p>

<p>Before I went for the business trip.</p>

<p>When I came back to Dandong. I got the package. And wear it.<!--more--></p>

<p>But on Saturday, I lost it. When I found it is gone, it is 2 or more hours later. I think it is lost when I ride the bicycle to east.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/11_23_the-cross.html">http://baham.co/11_23_the-cross.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting in the Jining Nan Station]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_16_waiting-in-the-jining-nan-station.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-16T07:39:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/waiting-in-the-jining-nan-station</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today, We, Hao, Dong and me went to the Jining, and Hao and I prepared to go to Linhe.</p>

<p>Originally, I thought we can came Jining by car and arrive at the station before 11:00 am. But the drivers can not go for the snow on the road. And Hao told us change the subway tickets to the later. So I did though this need be considering more. But finally, we came before 11:00, but the early tickets are sold out all.</p>

<p>So we need wait in Jining more than 8 hours.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>As me, all the time, I dislike wasting time, dislike just waiting. For life is short, man always ned save time.</p>

<p>And 8 hours&#8217; waiting is not the worse. When we had launch. Hao said went to the station to wait, originally, I thought maybe we can have a rest in the motel. But since the boss said waiting, I thought just do waiting.</p>

<p>But when we got in the station, maybe half a hour later, he said I waited here and took care of the baggage, he wanted to take a stroll. For now, it is nearly 4 hours. He the boss still did nt came back. And I still stayed and took care of the luggage.</p>

<p>Didn&rsquo;t I dislike taking a stroll in a place that I have not visited? Didn&rsquo;t I like taking care of the baggage? Didn&rsquo;t I like sit on a hard seat?</p>

<p>But these all doesn&rsquo;t matter. After all, God told us, <code>Let every soul be subject unto the higher powers. For there is no power but of God: the powers that be are ordained of God.</code>(Romans-13:1)</p>

<p>And I use this time to remember the English words, reading bible and listening the psalmes. I did not waste much time.</p>

<p>But is this a boss or a leader ought to do. Just leave the personnel alone to take care of the baggage and travel and have fun himself. I do not think so.</p>

<p>Maybe this article is not a positive one, and it is not to bring uo and train man. And maybe there was some complain here. But I still wanted to write this article, and just notice myself, when doing things, care about others&#8217; feeling. And say out your opinion to the partner.</p>

<pre><code>And we know that all things work together for good to them that love God, to them who are the called according to his purpose.  --Romans-8:28
</code></pre>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/11_16_waiting-in-the-jining-nan-station.html">http://baham.co/11_16_waiting-in-the-jining-nan-station.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mongolia]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_12_mongolia.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-12T08:40:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/mongolia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my first time to go to Mongolia. There is an innovation porject here.</p>

<p>And Wang and I came.</p>

<p>Just on the road, we take about more than one day.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The sky is blue, the air is clean. Though I was a little tired. But still had a not bad emotion.</p>

<p>And you know this land is Empire Mongolia&rsquo;s base. So when I saw grassland. I thought of the history.</p>

<p>When I went into the city, I found the city in Mongolia is different with in inlands. The road is more wide, amount of people is more less.</p>

<p>And the small city is more like the America city in lots of films.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/11_12_mongolia.html">http://baham.co/11_12_mongolia.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[360wifi be evil]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_06_360wifi-be-evil.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-06T13:32:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/360wifi-be-evil</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="http://baham.co/images/360wifi/360wifi2.jpg" alt="360wifi" /></p>

<p>These days, I found there is a 360wifi on the public PC. So I got the ssid and the password to get the internet access.</p>

<p>But when I use this 360wifi to access internet. I found an evil thing 360 done.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>When I visit django</h2>

<p>I wanted to learn some knowledge about django. When I use my laptop to visit djangoproject.com, I got nothing, but a <em>Server Not Found</em></p>

<p><img src="http://baham.co/images/360wifi/snf.png" alt="server not found" /></p>

<p>But when I use the public pc that installed 360wifi, I can access djangoproject.com.</p>

<p><img src="http://baham.co/images/360wifi/django.png" alt="django" /></p>

<h2>Inference</h2>

<p>So I infer that 360wifi block some foreign websites. include:</p>

<p><a href="http://djangoproject.com">django</a>, turbogears, pip, and my vps&rsquo;s ip.</p>

<p>They are all blocked.</p>

<p>And I think there are more sites and ips were blocked by 360wifi.</p>

<h2>Others</h2>

<p>I do not know how about the similar products in China, like <em>baidu wifi</em> or <em>xiaomi wifi</em>.</p>

<h2>Questions</h2>

<p>I found this abnormal phenomenon, but I still did not know why.</p>

<p>I wanted to learn some about django or turbogears to build a site, but why 360wifi block them.</p>

<p>Did these sites include some bad things or bad plugins or even break the law? But you know, they are all open source project, and only for the developers to download software and get docs.</p>

<h2>Advise</h2>

<p>So my adivise is use a wireless network card instead of the 360wifi. Maybe using wireless network card is more difficult to config, but it is more safe and free.</p>

<pre><code>The Life is Short, Away from 360
</code></pre>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/11_06_360wifi-be-evil.html">http://baham.co/11_06_360wifi-be-evil.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Travel To Donggang by Bicycle]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_02_travel-to-donggang-by-bicycle.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-02T13:09:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/travel-to-donggang-by-bicycle</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I bought a bicycle weeks ago, a mountain bike. It cost me more than half of my month salary. (Of course, my salary is pretty low) lol.</p>

<p>And today, I ride this bike with Wei who ride a Meride bicycle to travel to Donggang.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>In fact, the sistance between start and the end is more than 40 km, and we need to come back before night. So we strated to ride in the morning.</p>

<p>And this is my first time to ride so far.</p>

<p>There are strong wind. And we must faced it, this is a problem, and make us feel tired.</p>

<p>When we were on the road, we found this place.</p>

<p><img src="http://baham.co/images/donggang/xia.jpg" alt="xiachang" /></p>

<p>I think it is a place to get salt. Even I got some powder to tast. It is salty, but in fact, finally I found it is not the place to get salt.</p>

<p>It is the place for farmer to get shrimps &hellip;</p>

<p>And I saw the horizon.</p>

<p><img src="http://baham.co/images/donggang/horizon.jpg" alt="horizon" /></p>

<p>When we come bakc, I wanted to travel more, but Wei is tired and just wanted to went back as quick as we can. And I did not consider this that time, and I blame he is not good at watching map and insisted on findding a new way back.</p>

<p>So I did a wrong thing, just consider my own things and thoughts and did not consider the other&rsquo;s.</p>

<p>Finally, we went back along the old way.</p>

<p>Thanks God.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/11_02_travel-to-donggang-by-bicycle.html">http://baham.co/11_02_travel-to-donggang-by-bicycle.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Model Thinking on coursera]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_01_model-thinking-on-coursera.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-01T12:45:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/model-thinking-on-coursera</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Though I always delay on the quiz test date. But I still finish the third quizs.</p>

<p>Before this course, I only finished one mooc course.</p>

<p>It is about Chinese history, and taught by Chinese.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>And I will do my best to insist on this course. And learn more moocs in this year.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/11_01_model-thinking-on-coursera.html">http://baham.co/11_01_model-thinking-on-coursera.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Use CloudFlare as the site's CDN again]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/11_01_use-cloudflare-as-the-sites-cdn-again.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-01T07:38:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/use-cloudflare-as-the-sites-cdn-again</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://baham.co/05_25_kai-shi-shi-yong-an-quan-bao-cdnfu-wu-liao.html">Anquanbao</a> CDN is a CDN provider. And there is the CDN point in HK.</p>

<p>But today, I change the CDN provider to cloudflare like before. For I found the cloudflare is supportting free ssl.</p>

<p>So I choose cloudflare. And I found there are more apps supported on cloudflare. Some are really cool and helpful.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>And you can use the https to visit <a href="https://baham.co">baham.co</a>
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/11_01_use-cloudflare-as-the-sites-cdn-again.html">http://baham.co/11_01_use-cloudflare-as-the-sites-cdn-again.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[2 movies I watched these days]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/10_28_2-movies-i-watched-these-days.html"/>
    <updated>2014-10-28T13:57:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/2-movies-i-watched-these-days</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These days, I watched 2 movies alone. LOL!!!</p>

<p>All were from Hollywood.</p>

<p>One is Guard of Galaxy. A cool and science film.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Another is <em>Maze Runner</em>. A movie that main actors are teenagers. And revised by the same name sci-fi.</p>

<p>Men aspire after freedom. Though aspiring is with danger.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/10_28_2-movies-i-watched-these-days.html">http://baham.co/10_28_2-movies-i-watched-these-days.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Third Time a cowork advise me to do research direction]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/10_28_the-third-time-a-cowork-advise-me-to-do-research-direction.html"/>
    <updated>2014-10-28T13:56:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-third-time-a-cowork-advise-me-to-do-research-direction</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> I am learning mineral processing in my university. When I graduate and started to work, I came here and got my first job.</p>

<p> Maybe no position will satisfy a man in a company. And I believe all things depend on God. So I just follow the boss&rsquo;s opinion. And worked here do the designing direction job.</p>

<p> <!--more-->
 After the meeting between DFMC and <a href="andestc.cl">Andes</a> a young company from Chile, B and J told me maybe I was more suitable with the Researching direction job.</p>

<p> And this is the third time I heard the advise from cowork. For B have told me the advise before. This time, J even said she can help me talk to boss.  Really thanks her, but I did not accept her good willing, after all I had talked this with the boss.</p>

<p> For now, the researching direction job is building the <strong>Mineral Processing Expert System</strong> that I think I would do when I came here. But the boss let me do the designing direction, do some plant&rsquo;s automation solution design.</p>

<p> Days ago, I talked to the boss, I told him I was good at programming and I had got some knowlege about matlab and metsim which softwares researchers in the company used. But he refused, he did not refuse directly, but he just said the researching job need the man who got Master Degree {in fact, not all of researchers got master degree.) and it is more difficult and hard. Though I express I can work hard and I did not fear hard. He still refuse.</p>

<p> Between the talk, I found he already made decision and would not change. So I stop talking and just listen.</p>

<pre><code> Let every soul be subject unto the higher powers. For there is no power but of God: the powers that be are ordained of God.  Rom 13:1

 So I took the boss's advise and still worked in disign direction. Not because of his talk, but God's word.

 And thanks God.
</code></pre>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/10_28_the-third-time-a-cowork-advise-me-to-do-research-direction.html">http://baham.co/10_28_the-third-time-a-cowork-advise-me-to-do-research-direction.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dr Gao's report]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/10_28_dr-gaos-report.html"/>
    <updated>2014-10-28T13:56:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/dr-gaos-report</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>On one Sunday, I was at KFC in Wanda to learn some English lecture about words. Bo called me, told me go back to the company to have a meeting.</p>

<p>When I knew the message, it is after 3 pm, and the meeting have already started. So I run my bicycle fast to come back.</p>

<p>Luckily, when I reached, the meeting had not started.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The reporter is Gao. who graduated from NEU and lived in AUS now. He report some new information and technology about the Australian Mineral Processing. Some bigger and newer machines.</p>

<p>And some new theories in foreign.</p>

<p>Like, SAG flowsheet, SAB, SABC flowsheet. And in froth flotation, how to control the separation and measure what.</p>

<p>Which is the best bubble&rsquo;s diameter in flotation? And you know the company is building the Mineral Processing Expert System. So Gao said some about expert system and JKmetsim that I knew but never used and touched software.</p>

<p>This is a good experiment.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/10_28_dr-gaos-report.html">http://baham.co/10_28_dr-gaos-report.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[China's Transgenic Calibration]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/10_28_chinas-transgenic-calibration.html"/>
    <updated>2014-10-28T13:53:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/chinas-transgenic-calibration</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Maybe a few people care about China&rsquo;s trangenic calibration.</p>

<h2>Before, China&rsquo;s transgenic food was qualitatively calibrated.</h2>

<p>If the food include transgenic part, than calibrated it &lsquo;Transgenic&rsquo;.</p>

<p>But in fact, like other regulations in China, a lot of people think the aim did not achieve. A lot of food whith &lsquo;Transgenic&rsquo; did not be calibrated. And the food without transgenic part calibrated with &lsquo;non-transgenic&rsquo;.</p>

<h2>And Now, China&rsquo;s transgenic food will be quantitatively calibrated.</h2>

<p>In fact, I thought this is a regression. But the medium did not say it is a regression, they said US/ Japan do like this too.</p>

<p>So this is the problem.</p>

<p>For me,
I do not care how much transgenic part a food have, I just care whether it has or not. Although, I probably had aten transgenic food with I have no idea which food have.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/10_28_chinas-transgenic-calibration.html">http://baham.co/10_28_chinas-transgenic-calibration.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Notes 1 of Model Thinking -Universoty of Michigan]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/10_09_model-thinking-universoty-of-michigan.html"/>
    <updated>2014-10-09T13:25:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/model-thinking-universoty-of-michigan</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I join this lecture.</p>

<p>And listen some video courses.</p>

<p>And make some notes.</p>

<!--more-->


<h2>Advantages of Model:</h2>

<ol>
<li>Intelligent Citizon of the World</li>
<li>Clearer thinker</li>
<li>Use and Understand data</li>
<li>Decide, Strategize and Design</li>
</ol>


<h2>Some words</h2>

<p>anthropology    人类学
zoology         动物学
logical incosistencies      逻辑矛盾
crutch          拐杖</p>

<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/10_09_model-thinking-universoty-of-michigan.html">http://baham.co/10_09_model-thinking-universoty-of-michigan.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[On The Road]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/10_01_the-octobor-1st.html"/>
    <updated>2014-10-01T03:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-octobor-1st</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today is Octobor 1st, another PRC&rsquo;s National Day. I am going back to home.</p>

<p>And I take some local speciality for the family.</p>

<p>After working in DFMC about 2 minths, a period time&rsquo;s puzzlling, thinking and praying.</p>

<p>I make a decision.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I want to go abroad next year.</p>

<!--
If you can finish your job very easily, you should get another job.

-->


<p> <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/10_01_the-octobor-1st.html">http://baham.co/10_01_the-octobor-1st.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Catching Crabs]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/09_30_catching-crabs.html"/>
    <updated>2014-09-30T13:05:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/catching-crabs</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Days ago, 2 roommates and I went to the China&rsquo;s side of Yalu River to catch the crabs in the evnening.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>And this is my first time to catch crabs. When I was a child, I had caught dragonfly, frogs and butterfly. But not crabs, for where I live is not near river.</p>

<p>Now, always feel that childhood is beaytiful.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/09_30_catching-crabs.html">http://baham.co/09_30_catching-crabs.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Bad Word]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/09_18_a-bad-word.html"/>
    <updated>2014-09-18T13:48:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/a-bad-word</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These days, I got cold. Today is the third day. And I say a wrong word. Orginally, I just want to say a joke. But I found it is bad a bad even evil word. Because I spoke so lordly that someone turn back to see my position.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I am not veru happy, bacause of the cold, the word from the Aunt in dinning hall(I asked her a lunch box, she refused.) and the others&#8217; talking about I using my left hand to eat.</p>

<p>In this time, to think the reson, it is nothing to make me unhappy, I feel.</p>

<p>And Jiao aksed me why use left hand? I wanted to say a joke, so say &lsquo;Why you have so much why?&rsquo; loudly.</p>

<p>It is not polite to her and others in the dinning hall though she did not care it. But I say it. And after the word, I felt really sorry.</p>

<p>I did a bad thing and said a bad word.</p>

<p><code>Therewith bless we God, even the Father; and therewith curse we men, which are made after the similitude of God.</code>  &mdash;James 3:9
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/09_18_a-bad-word.html">http://baham.co/09_18_a-bad-word.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Goldendict Support Mdx]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/09_11_goldendict-support-mdx.html"/>
    <updated>2014-09-11T12:14:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/goldendict-support-mdx</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I started to use <a href="http://goldendict.org/">goldendict</a> since stardict is down. Maybe it is the best dict software on Linux.</p>

<p>So I still keep using it.</p>

<p>But I do not notice which time godendict started to supprot mdx. You know it is very strong, .mdx dictionary.</p>

<p>Because since <a href="http://www.octopus-studio.com/">Rayman Zhang</a> created this software. Lots of men create the dictionaries for mdict with .mdx.</p>

<p>I use the mdict since years ago, that time I still use the windows mobile smart phone.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>These days, I got a new pc from the compony for work, so I want to install golden dict on windows too. But I found the version I downloaded is still 1, and vesion 1 did not support mdx. So I found this link, the goldendict&rsquo;s early access build for windows.</p>

<p><a href="https://github.com/goldendict/goldendict/wiki/Early-Access-Builds-for-Windows">goldendict 1.5 rc</a></p>

<p>Enjoy it!</p>

<p>And, source code here <a href="https://github.com/goldendict/goldendict/">goldendict source code</a>
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/09_11_goldendict-support-mdx.html">http://baham.co/09_11_goldendict-support-mdx.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Second Business Trip]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/09_03_the-second-business-trip.html"/>
    <updated>2014-09-03T14:59:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-second-business-trip</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Xiong gave me a job, it is went to the Mineal Preparation Plant to do some information exchange work with Tao and make me know more about design automation project.</p>

<p> So we went to the mpp. It is far away from DD. The most of time of the business trip time is on the road.</p>

<p>Maybe you can not believe it.</p>

<p>This picture cameraed in the Mpp.</p>

<p><img src="http://baham.co/images/business/jrs.jpg" alt="jrs" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>But it is reall, I think maybe this thing can only happened in China.</p>

<p>The trip is kind of well.</p>

<p>So we exchange requiest and ideas with the Compony A. And I do some recording work. We went to the mpp to see the detail of the plant.</p>

<p>Then we went back.</p>

<p>What I found from this business trip is business trip is not an easy work, cause maybe you will take most of trip time on the road.
 <p class='post-footer' style="font-size:70%;" ></p>

<br/>


<br/>


<br/>


<p>The Original Link: <a href="http://baham.co/09_03_the-second-business-trip.html">http://baham.co/09_03_the-second-business-trip.html</a><br/>
If you want to reprint it, please do under the  <a rel="nofollow" href=/license>CC BY-NC-SA 4.0</a>
</p></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
