<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Travel | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/travel/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2014-08-19T14:14:13+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Travel to Hekou]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/08_16_travel-to-hekou.html"/>
    <updated>2014-08-16T11:01:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/travel-to-hekou</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> This is the first Group Travel since I came to the company. And the distination is Hekou Village, it is near North Korea.</p>

<p> Maybe the Dining Hall knew we will travel, so it prepare us this- &lsquo;Liangpi&rsquo; in Chinese.</p>

<p><img src="/images/hekou/liangpi.jpg" alt="liangpi" /></p>

<p>Maybe it tastes delicious, but if you are hungry, after eating it, you will be still hungry.</p>

<p>After dinner, we set out.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Hekou is not very far from Dandong, just about 100 minutes. Where we live is a peasant&rsquo;s house, his family name is Zhao. After arranging the beds, we came to the port, and get a ship to visit the palces near Yalu River.</p>

<p><img src="/images/hekou/fisherman.jpg" alt="fisherman" /></p>

<p>The pictures showed Korean fishermen fishing.</p>

<p>And we travel on the ship along the river.</p>

<p>When we came back to the port, Yu want to swim. And the only one girl Jiao went to the shop to buy some little things.</p>

<p>And we found this old plane, <img src="/iamges/hekou/airplane.jpg" alt="plane" /></p>

<p>And a tank,</p>

<p><img src="/images/hekou/tank.jpg" alt="tank" /></p>

<p>And who is near the tank is our bus driver. He is a hardworking driver.</p>

<p>This is a happy day.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[About 3 hours in Zhengzhou]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/04_27_3-hours-in-zhengzhou.html"/>
    <updated>2014-04-27T02:57:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/3-hours-in-zhengzhou</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When I was in Pingdingshan, I need to came back to Xuzhou City to get my debit card.</p>

<p>So I asked 2 day for leave.</p>

<p>But the ticket of train from Pingdingshan to Xuzhou with a chair is gone. So I bought a ticket from Pingdingshan to Zhengzhou and a ticket from Zhengzhou to Xuzhou.</p>

<p>So I have about 3 hours to travel in Zhengzhou and to wait for the train.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Zhengzhou City is a big city in central China. It is the biggest city in Henan. Its name ccame from the Zheng Kingdom in Zhou Dynasty.</p>

<p>I did not really travel there, just bought something and wook the subway to the banks to ask about the visa debit card. Cause you know I need a visa card to pay the mensa test fee. That time, I think maybe there were some big backs would support some visa or master debit card. And I think the cards would get at once. In fact, my thought was wrong.</p>

<p>But it is not a bad experience. Cause I saw something.</p>

<p>I saw this poster on the wall near the road. And in winter holiday, I saw them in my hometown too.</p>

<p><img src="/images/zz/gd.jpg" alt="gd" /></p>

<p>There are 3 words there, maybe you can not understand them. Sincerely, I did not understand them too.</p>

<p>But the translations to English were:</p>

<ol>
<li>Thanks! My Country and parents!</li>
<li>Sing a folk song for the P!</li>
<li>Long Live the P!</li>
</ol>


<p>I really can not understand these words. It is like in a old kingdom country not like in a modern country.</p>

<p>And this is show a phenomnon in China, Nearly everyone dislike the p, but most of people still want to be the member. maybe they want to get the power, the economic power, the trust by g.o.v and so on. So sometimes they lie.</p>

<p>And there another picture in tunnel of  Zhengzhou subway station.</p>

<p><img src="/images/zz/gd2.jpg" alt="gd2" /></p>

<p>It means &ldquo;Why China can be so strong? Cause we have the p.&rdquo;</p>

<p>And I take a photo about this building.</p>

<p><img src="/images/zz/atower.jpg" alt="atowerinzhengzhou" /></p>

<p>It make me think of Tower Defense Games, like dota. LoL!!!</p>

<p>The p means <img src="/images/zz/p.jpg" alt="p" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exchange Dream by Jiaqian]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/04_26_exchange-dream-by-jiaqian.html"/>
    <updated>2014-04-26T01:46:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/exchange-dream-by-jiaqian</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The first day in Guangzhou City, there is the Exchange Dream by Jiaqian.</p>

<p>So when I went to Sun Yat-sen University to join in it.</p>

<p>It is my second time to take Guangzhou Train. And when got there, I didn&rsquo;t know where is north. So I thount and found it by the building&rsquo;s  window(You know although in sourth of China, people still build the big window to sourth).</p>

<p>And with the map, I found the university. But I did not get it, so I asked a passby, he told me the position.</p>

<p><img src="/images/guangdong/sunyatsen.jpg" alt="sun-yat-sen-university" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>So I went to the classroom where the Exchange Dream started. I foung it before the activity started. And I was hungry, though I had a Niunan Noodle on the road to train stop, the noodle tasted really bad. So I asked a girl where is refectory or dining hall.</p>

<p>She gave me a direction but it is not very clear. Then I went out of the classroom to the refectory.</p>

<p>I did not found it, I walked back and asked a passby. She told me she went there too that I can followed her. And we went the refectory together.</p>

<p>On the road, we talk a few things about the Sun Yat-sen University , her major and why I was here.</p>

<p>Then I arrived in the refectory, I bought a meal ticket, and took some rice and some vegetables to eat(like Popeye the Sailor).</p>

<p>After the dinner, I went back to the calssroom. It is about 7 pm, but Jiaqian was still not arrive.</p>

<p>We waited for about 2/3 hour. She came. And I shared a story about my entering a higher school. And listend more stories from others.</p>

<p>The number of viewers in Sun Yat-sen is less than CUMT. But there are more interesting stories.</p>

<p>And the two girls who was left from me are just hign school students, so young and so cute.</p>

<p>A girl shared her childhood and love story, another girl shared her hairstyle and she how to bet with her deskmate, a boy just standed there until the activity stoped &hellip;
<img src="/images/guangdong/jiaqian.jpg" alt="exchangedream" />
After it, I went back by train. It is so late, so I took a shower, watche a little TV and just slept for tomorrow&rsquo;s test.</p>

<p>Oh there is a very cool thing in Sun Yat-Sen University, an old style&rsquo;s washing room.
<img src="/images/guangdong/wc.jpg" alt="wc" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Travel in Shenzhen City]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/04_24_shenzhen.html"/>
    <updated>2014-04-24T11:04:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/shenzhen</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>You know Shenzhen is the most biggest 4 cities in China. And it is a Special Area in Ecnomic. And a citizen in Shenzhen can go to Hongkong freely. But the citizens in other part of China can not.</p>

<p>Sicerely, Shenzhen is a pretty fashion and open city. But there are still some China&rsquo;s Characteristics in Shenzhen.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>When I arrive in Luohu Port, I saw some young men sell milk powder. I do not know these young men are from Hongkong or Mainland, but they just sit near the port and sell the milk powder.</p>

<p>In China, there is an incident happend that milk powder is posionous. And some babies got sick by the posionous milk powder.</p>

<p>So someone smuggle milk powder from HK to CN.</p>

<p>And this is my first time to experience to see the milk powder from HK.</p>

<p>Out of the port building, there are a lot of people selling goods(I guess they are smuggled goods) in the square. There are too many to count the number.</p>

<p><img src="/images/guangdong/smuggle.jpg" alt="Smuggler" /></p>

<p>The square is near the port and train station. And there are policemen or city managers. But they still sell the goods. And no policemen or city managers care about them. You know smugglling break the law.</p>

<p>I think because even policemen or city managers also want their babies have no-posion milk powder.</p>

<p>After the travel near the port. I went on the train to see the sea.</p>

<p>Follow the map&rsquo;s direction, I came to A train stop near the sea.</p>

<p>And I walked to sourth by my feet.</p>

<p>I go across a residential district and in map, it is near the sea.</p>

<p>So I walked and foung the beach. Until I saw a tunnel under the highway. I go pass it. And I saw an armed policeman camp, but I did not care it and still went following the map.</p>

<p>I walked and walked, there was a cross.</p>

<p>2 policemen saw me and asked me what was I doing.</p>

<p>And I told them I came here to see the sea and the mangrove. And something about me.</p>

<p>They told me I can not come here, Here was never opened for people.</p>

<p>So I turend and go back.</p>

<p>They after me on the bikes, one on the bike told me he can give a drive.</p>

<p>I thanked go on the bike. So they take me out of forbidden zone. We talked on the road. They two were just  as young as me. They are kind, and told me go to the Mangrove Stop to see the sea and mangrove in Shenzhen.</p>

<p>Then I followed their advise to take the taxi there.</p>

<p>When I arrived, it is already dark.</p>

<p>I felt the wind from the Shenzhen Bay and saw the bustling and flourishing buildings in Shenzhen and the bridge between Shenzhen and Honkong.</p>

<p>Then I went back to the Shenzhen Train Station and went to Guangdong.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Go to Shenzhen]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/04_21_go-to-shenzhen.html"/>
    <updated>2014-04-21T10:46:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/go-to-shenzhen</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There is a old word in China, it is <em>to Travel Thousands Miles is More Than to Read Thousands Books</em>.</p>

<p>Before I got to Guangzhen, I decided to travel to Shenzhen after the mensa test in Guangzhou.</p>

<p>So at about 15:00 April 19, I arrived the train to Shenzhen. After about 90 minutes. I arrived Shenzhen City.</p>

<p>I had only two purposes.</p>

<p>One is to watch Honkong, the other is to see sea.</p>

<p>After I got out of the train station. I bought a map of Shenzhen. And I found Luohu Port is just near the train station.</p>

<p>So I walked to Luohu Port.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>But when I arrive the port. I found you can see nothing.</p>

<p>There is a port building <img src="/images/guangdong/luohuport.jpg" alt="luohuport" />
and after the building , there is a police station,
after the station, there are mountains.</p>

<p>You know, In the media in China, they always insist on that Hongkong is one part of China. But I a Chinese went to Hongkong is more difficult than a foreigner. This is a really bad thing.</p>

<p>In the back of the port building , I take a picture with my phones&rsquo;s camera.</p>

<p><img src="/images/guangdong/bird.jpg" alt="HK CN bird" /></p>

<p>A bird can fly over the port freely, but a man can not.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
