<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Job | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.github.io/blog/categories/job/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2015-08-18T00:56:34+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Dogs and The Smile]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.github.io/11_27_the-dogs-and-the-smile.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-27T10:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.github.io/the-dogs-and-the-smile</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> On the noon, when I had my lunch, I still take the rest food of mine to feed the dogs, that I found about month ago.</p>

<p> Days earlier, still on the noon. When I went dowstairs, there was still a woman there fo feed the dogs with milk. And I got some information about the dogs from her.</p>

<p> The mom dod bore the child dogs here, and it is a homeless dog. So now the three are all homeless.</p>

<p> And for me, I found the mom dog in a night when I debug my bicycle. In that time, I still do not know its nest, neither not its child dogs.</p>

<p>But today noon, <!--more-->
When I fed them. The mom dog did not bark to me. This the fourth day since I take them food.</p>

<p>And I smile, and felt happy. Really happy! When I saw it the scene.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Waiting in the Jining Nan Station]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.github.io/11_16_waiting-in-the-jining-nan-station.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-16T07:39:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.github.io/waiting-in-the-jining-nan-station</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today, We, Hao, Dong and me went to the Jining, and Hao and I prepared to go to Linhe.</p>

<p>Originally, I thought we can came Jining by car and arrive at the station before 11:00 am. But the drivers can not go for the snow on the road. And Hao told us change the subway tickets to the later. So I did though this need be considering more. But finally, we came before 11:00, but the early tickets are sold out all.</p>

<p>So we need wait in Jining more than 8 hours.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>As me, all the time, I dislike wasting time, dislike just waiting. For life is short, man always ned save time.</p>

<p>And 8 hours' waiting is not the worse. When we had launch. Hao said went to the station to wait, originally, I thought maybe we can have a rest in the motel. But since the boss said waiting, I thought just do waiting.</p>

<p>But when we got in the station, maybe half a hour later, he said I waited here and took care of the baggage, he wanted to take a stroll. For now, it is nearly 4 hours. He the boss still did nt came back. And I still stayed and took care of the luggage.</p>

<p>Didn&rsquo;t I dislike taking a stroll in a place that I have not visited? Didn&rsquo;t I like taking care of the baggage? Didn&rsquo;t I like sit on a hard seat?</p>

<p>But these all doesn&rsquo;t matter. After all, God told us, <code>Let every soul be subject unto the higher powers. For there is no power but of God: the powers that be are ordained of God.</code>(Romans-13:1)</p>

<p>And I use this time to remember the English words, reading bible and listening the psalmes. I did not waste much time.</p>

<p>But is this a boss or a leader ought to do. Just leave the personnel alone to take care of the baggage and travel and have fun himself. I do not think so.</p>

<p>Maybe this article is not a positive one, and it is not to bring uo and train man. And maybe there was some complain here. But I still wanted to write this article, and just notice myself, when doing things, care about others' feeling. And say out your opinion to the partner.</p>

<pre><code>And we know that all things work together for good to them that love God, to them who are the called according to his purpose.  --Romans-8:28
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mongolia]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.github.io/11_12_mongolia.html"/>
    <updated>2014-11-12T08:40:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.github.io/mongolia</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my first time to go to Mongolia. There is an innovation porject here.</p>

<p>And Wang and I came.</p>

<p>Just on the road, we take about more than one day.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>The sky is blue, the air is clean. Though I was a little tired. But still had a not bad emotion.</p>

<p>And you know this land is Empire Mongolia&rsquo;s base. So when I saw grassland. I thought of the history.</p>

<p>When I went into the city, I found the city in Mongolia is different with in inlands. The road is more wide, amount of people is more less.</p>

<p>And the small city is more like the America city in lots of films.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Third Time a cowork advise me to do research direction]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.github.io/10_28_the-third-time-a-cowork-advise-me-to-do-research-direction.html"/>
    <updated>2014-10-28T13:56:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.github.io/the-third-time-a-cowork-advise-me-to-do-research-direction</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> I am learning mineral processing in my university. When I graduate and started to work, I came here and got my first job.</p>

<p> Maybe no position will satisfy a man in a company. And I believe all things depend on God. So I just follow the boss&rsquo;s opinion. And worked here do the designing direction job.</p>

<p> <!--more-->
 After the meeting between DFMC and <a href="andestc.cl">Andes</a> a young company from Chile, B and J told me maybe I was more suitable with the Researching direction job.</p>

<p> And this is the third time I heard the advise from cowork. For B have told me the advise before. This time, J even said she can help me talk to boss.  Really thanks her, but I did not accept her good willing, after all I had talked this with the boss.</p>

<p> For now, the researching direction job is building the <strong>Mineral Processing Expert System</strong> that I think I would do when I came here. But the boss let me do the designing direction, do some plant&rsquo;s automation solution design.</p>

<p> Days ago, I talked to the boss, I told him I was good at programming and I had got some knowlege about matlab and metsim which softwares researchers in the company used. But he refused, he did not refuse directly, but he just said the researching job need the man who got Master Degree {in fact, not all of researchers got master degree.) and it is more difficult and hard. Though I express I can work hard and I did not fear hard. He still refuse.</p>

<p> Between the talk, I found he already made decision and would not change. So I stop talking and just listen.</p>

<pre><code> Let every soul be subject unto the higher powers. For there is no power but of God: the powers that be are ordained of God.  Rom 13:1

 So I took the boss's advise and still worked in disign direction. Not because of his talk, but God's word.

 And thanks God.
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Second Business Trip]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.github.io/09_03_the-second-business-trip.html"/>
    <updated>2014-09-03T14:59:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.github.io/the-second-business-trip</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> Xiong gave me a job, it is went to the Mineal Preparation Plant to do some information exchange work with Tao and make me know more about design automation project.</p>

<p> So we went to the mpp. It is far away from DD. The most of time of the business trip time is on the road.</p>

<p>Maybe you can not believe it.</p>

<p>This picture cameraed in the Mpp.</p>

<p><img src="/images/business/jrs.jpg" alt="jrs" /></p>

<!--more-->


<p>But it is reall, I think maybe this thing can only happened in China.</p>

<p>The trip is kind of well.</p>

<p>So we exchange requiest and ideas with the Compony A. And I do some recording work. We went to the mpp to see the detail of the plant.</p>

<p>Then we went back.</p>

<p>What I found from this business trip is business trip is not an easy work, cause maybe you will take most of trip time on the road.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
