<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Job | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/job/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2014-08-16T08:34:48+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Group in Younth Gellowship]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/08_14_the-group-in-younth-gellowship.html"/>
    <updated>2014-08-14T05:11:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-group-in-younth-gellowship</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These 2 days, I was busy at the <code>Flotation Agents Auto-Adding Machine</code>&rsquo;s debugging and testing. Because it will be sent to Jin Chuang Group to be tested by Mineral Preparation Plants.</p>

<p><img src="/images/dfmc/flotation.jpg" alt="flotation Agents" /></p>

<p>It is not difficult to do this. But it is complicated. And Liang still want me finishing the Ball Minn Machine data-check task.</p>

<p>But after I came back yesterday, I foung it is the time to go to the cell group meeting, and it woulb be my first time to go to the cell group on Dandong.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I left the company after eating dinner at the dinning hall. Then I went to the place last time Dong told me.</p>

<p>On the road, I met Yi, and we went together a while. When I got there, it is still about 20 minutes before the meeting time.</p>

<p>And in the department the house hold,  there were already 2 brothers, one is Guo, another is Geng. Because of talking, I knew Guo just came back from North Korea. He went to NK nor for Travel, but for Gospel. Though he is younger than me, but what he did I think is more meaningful.</p>

<p>This meeting, we pray, we talk, and about 3 hours later, we left. And this is my first time to listen so much talk from brothers and sisters after I graduated.</p>

<p><code>For where two or three are gathered together in my name, there am I in the midst of them.</code> &mdash;Mattew 1:20</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I built a Flotation Separator with blender]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/08_01_i-built-a-floation-separator-with-blender.html"/>
    <updated>2014-08-01T00:58:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/i-built-a-floation-separator-with-blender</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img src="/images/mineral/flotation1.jpg" alt="Flotation Separator" />
Boss Xie had talked with us fresh men about the 3D moduling, he thought the studio need men to build 3D module. And I can kind of use <em>Blender</em>, I told him this.</p>

<p>After this talk, I started learning and using blender again. Though I had no books to watch. But there are many tutorials in my disk, after all, blender is an open software. A few days ago, I finished this flotation separator.<!--more--></p>

<p><img src="/images/mineral/flotation2.jpg" alt="FS" /></p>

<p>It is not very cool, or verisimilitude. But at least, when I show this to Biao, he can recognize it.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The First Week's Salary]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_25_the-first-weeks-salary.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-25T12:43:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-first-weeks-salary</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>A few days ago, I got my firsk week&rsquo;s salary. It is not too much, just a few hundred yuan.<!--more--> But it is really meaningful.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Seven Days' Train]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_17_seven-days-train.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-17T09:19:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/seven-days-train</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I did not worked in 7 Days Hotel, not lived in &lsquo;7 Days&rsquo; either.</p>

<p>Because the company prepare 7 days to train us, freshmen.</p>

<p>What we do between the train, is learning and knowing each other.</p>

<p>And you know, I am not very good at making friends, or remember new guys. So, in the first several days, I did not do well at knowing each other. But in the last several days, when we knew more about each other, our relashionship is more close.<!--more--></p>

<p>Most of time, I did not drink to avoid being drunk, this time, I drink some beer. When you drink, you want to talk, so I talked more than ever, but I still have clear mind to control my mouth.</p>

<p><code>Let us walk honestly, as in the day; not in rioting and drunkenness, not in chambering and wantonness, not in strife and envying. </code>  &mdash;Romans 13:13</p>

<p>And between the 7 days train, there are 2 teachers/ministers' talk I can not forget. One is the minister of planning department &mdash; Mr Wang, the other is the vice general manager &mdash;Mr Fan.</p>

<p>Wang talked one book&mdash;<em>Secret</em>, the book belongs to New Age Movement. Before I left CUMT, at the last church meeting,  Duan taught us how to distinguish heresy. And she remind us of the New Age Movement and the book <em>Secret</em>.  Maybe Mr Wang is member of the Party, maybe he is not. But what he talked really did not suit the communism, or athesim, and did not suit the Christianity either. And I really want to talk about the religion with him, make him know Jesus.</p>

<p>As Mr Fan, he is smart. He talked a lot. About value of man, about wealth, about work, his experience and so on. And one thing he talked make me remember him. He said &ldquo;Men need Belief, professing a belief in Christianity is more than without belief.&rdquo; And as this word, I do not know wether he has join the Church meeting, and I did not know how to reply, or how to explain the difference of  the belief he said and the belief beliver profess in. So I said nothing, and just listened.</p>

<p>And Fan said men shouldn&rsquo;t attach great importance to wealth, I agrre with him about this, though I am not wealthy. But, after his word, some one express different opinion, said his opinion is all by he is already wealthy.</p>

<p>Men need belief, China needs belief. But communism is not a belief, money is not either.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Muslim Girl I Know]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_15_a-muslim-girl-i-know.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-15T05:41:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/a-muslim-girl-i-know</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>There is a Muslim girl in company. I kind of knew her, but she did not. Because when we were still at school to find jobs. I saw her a lot of times in application meeting. And sometimes she introduce herself, I was still at the meeting. And got some information about her. Of cause, I did not do this by purpose. Maybe she did not remember me. But I remembered her. Because she is a Muslim and a Hui nationality girl, and has a boyfriend who is Han nationality, and she had joined one and only one students organization &mdash;Stage Show Organization. And you know I am fan of CUMT Stage Show.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I did not knew her came to the same compony as me until I found her name in the QQ group. And I had talked to her about why came here so far away from her home, she replied me she got this offer firstly.</p>

<p>In one application meeting, I found her is in too. And the HR asked her about her religion and what she is different form Han nationality girl. I generally remember she replied although she is a Hui nationality girl, but after she came to the university, she eat with classmates who are not Muslim, and she has a boyfriend who is a Han nantionality boy.</p>

<p>Though the HR did not say his opinion, did not say why he did not accept her. But that time I felt the HR rejudice her. Not rejudice her grades, or her appearance or her ability. He rejudice her religion. He worried the difference between Han and Hui will make some mistake in the fulture in the compony, though she said she already adopt Han&rsquo;s traditions and habits. The HR&rsquo;s worry is not gone.</p>

<p>Why I write this and why I remeber this, because one day when we ate in the same desktop. I found when she ate, she just eat a few kinds of dishes(without pork). Maybe when she came dfmc&rsquo;s application meeting, she did not emphasize her religion. And the company did not prepare the Islamic food for her. And when I saw this, I really really symphathize her. And I really want to tell her what you eat or waht you did not eat can not make you be saved, or make you be liked by God.</p>

<p>I wanted to, but I really do not know how to, and dare not to. I am a Christian, when I introduce myself, I will tell the listeners, including her, a Muslim. And she is a Muslim, she did not emphasize this. But when she sat before the desktop, I really can not understand her feeling or her thoughts about the food with pork.</p>

<p>I want to help her, not because she is a classmate of mine, not because she is a pretty girl, just because I want to, and not only  her, but also the Koren over the river, and the men who did not believe the God&hellip;&hellip;</p>

<p>May God bless.</p>

<p><code>For God so loved the world, that he gave his only begotten Son, that whosoever believeth in him should not perish, but have everlasting life.</code>  &mdash;John3:16</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
