<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Faith | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/faith/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2015-05-29T11:54:24+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Group in Younth Fellowship]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/08_14_the-group-in-younth-gellowship.html"/>
    <updated>2014-08-14T05:11:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/the-group-in-younth-gellowship</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These 2 days, I was busy at the <code>Flotation Agents Auto-Adding Machine</code>&rsquo;s debugging and testing. Because it will be sent to Jin Chuang Group to be tested by Mineral Preparation Plants.</p>

<p><img src="/images/dfmc/flotation.jpg" alt="flotation Agents" /></p>

<p>It is not difficult to do this. But it is complicated. And Liang still want me finishing the Ball Minn Machine data-check task.</p>

<p>But after I came back yesterday, I foung it is the time to go to the cell group meeting, and it woulb be my first time to go to the cell group on Dandong.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I left the company after eating dinner at the dinning hall. Then I went to the place last time Dong told me.</p>

<p>On the road, I met Yi, and we went together a while. When I got there, it is still about 20 minutes before the meeting time.</p>

<p>And in the department the house hold,  there were already 2 brothers, one is Guo, another is Geng. Because of talking, I knew Guo just came back from North Korea. He went to NK nor for Travel, but for Gospel. Though he is younger than me, but what he did I think is more meaningful.</p>

<p>This meeting, we pray, we talk, and about 3 hours later, we left. And this is my first time to listen so much talk from brothers and sisters after I graduated.</p>

<p><code>For where two or three are gathered together in my name, there am I in the midst of them.</code> &mdash;Mattew 1:20</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[First Time To Read All Contents of Bible]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_25_first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-25T12:50:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/first-time-to-read-all-contents-of-bible</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tonight, I read the <em>Malachi</em>, the last one in Old Testament.</p>

<p>Since September 2013, I started to read Bible. And I finshed reading all content of Holy Bible.</p>

<p>Write this post to remember this day.</p>

<!--more-->

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Church Meeting and Baptsim]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_22_church-meeting-and-baptsim.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-22T12:47:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/church-meeting-and-baptsim</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday is a Saturday, we attended church meeting. The teacher is from Taian, the subject is about Faith, Heresy, Her Witness and Fundamentals.</p>

<p>I was attracted with this. After I finished my procedures of graduation, I stayed in the church to listen the teaching.</p>

<p>And the teaching stoped at about 5:00 pm, then I went to be baptized.</p>

<p>This is a really rare chance to be baptized. Since I came to CUMT Fellowship, I found I was changed, and a few month ago, I found I wanted to be baptized. And this is the last chance to be baptized before graduation.</p>

<p>Really thanks God. Because he gave me this changce.</p>

<p>About baptsim. There are a lot of words in Bible.<!--more--></p>

<p><code>He that believeth and is baptized shall be saved; but he that believeth not shall be damned. --Mark 16:16</code></p>

<p><code>Therefore if any man be in Christ, he is a new creature: old things are passed away; behold, all things are become new. --Corinthians 5:17</code></p>

<p>And there is a witness about Philip and an eunuch.</p>

<p>The reason that I want to be baptized is only one, I want to be saved.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Graduate]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/06_16_graduate.html"/>
    <updated>2014-06-16T06:27:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/graduate</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Yesterday, brothers and sisters got together to learn God&rsquo;s words and say goodbye to graduates, like me.</p>

<p>I came to the fellowship in September 2013, and now I will leave.</p>

<p>And I find a difference between I came and I left, before I came to the fellowship, I had a heart made up of stone, but now I feel my heart is made up of flesh. What or who gave me this difference, I thing is God&rsquo;s words, it is Bible, it is Spirit.</p>

<p>I always thought I would not be sad when I graduate. But I find I am wrong, now. Because I feel sadness.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Before noon, Mrs Zhang call me to ask me about how to get water. And I just came to the fellowship.
I arrived at about 12:30, and there are many elders and classmates, I felt sleepy, cause I had a habit to sleep at noon.</p>

<p>I did not know how to say. So I just write it sorted by the time.</p>

<p>I bought steamed breads and condiments.</p>

<p>We sang songs to admire and praise God.</p>

<p>Pastor Lu gave us a lesson about how to keep the faith after graduatation in this guilty World.</p>

<p>A presentation of graduates, and I am the first, I did not prepare fot it.</p>

<p>Receiving the gifts and elders gave us a blessing and lesson(Pastor Yao and Aunt Diao and so on).</p>

<p>Cells' shows, and I paly a harmonica show and sang it  /simple gift/.</p>

<p>We lined in 2 circles and said goodbye.</p>

<p>We ate. There are really many people this time. Maybe 40-50 people.</p>

<p><code>I really don't know how to describe this day, what I can do is just write the title and keep the memory in my mind.</code></p>

<p>Thanks God!</p>

<p><code>And he answering said, Thou shalt love the Lord thy God with all thy heart, and with all thy soul, and with all thy strength, and with all thy mind; and thy neighbour as thyself.</code>  &mdash;Luke 10:27</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Jesus knows Your pain]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_29_jesus-knows-your-pain.html"/>
    <updated>2014-05-29T08:02:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/jesus-knows-your-pain</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>These 2 days, I just do one thing. It is writing my paper and instruction to the coal preparation plant I designed.</p>

<p>But this is one thing very bad , it is the college tell me to submit the instruction/paper/translation in may 29. But the noticed is opened at may 27.</p>

<p>And what I prayed to say Jesus is help me to give me strength and time to write the instuction. Cause I have not writen the instruction.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>And this notice made me unhappy.</p>

<p>Really unhappy.</p>

<p>But I gave this burden to Jesus, and search the help from Jesus.</p>

<p>I wake up at May 28, and I just write the words to the instruction.</p>

<p>I did not finished it by the night. And I slept at about 23 pm.</p>

<p>There is another thing make me unhappy. Cause I need to take physical examination at May 2y the same day as the submitting day.</p>

<p>These 2 days, I ate, I slept, I talked, I joined to Bible Study Group, But I was unhappy.</p>

<p>Until a little time later, I check my instruction and paper and so on with the check-paper too to verify whether my artcile had high repetition rate.</p>

<p>I got 10 percents. And the college&rsquo;s reqiurement is 20 percents.</p>

<p>Really thanks God.</p>

<pre><code>Hitherto have ye asked nothing in my name: ask, and ye shall receive, that your joy may be full.   --John 16;24
</code></pre>

<p>Jesus Really felt my pain and helped me. What love he gave!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
