<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Faith | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/faith/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2014-05-14T11:09:22+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Labor Day's Church Meeting]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/05_02_church-meeting-in-worker-s-day.html"/>
    <updated>2014-05-02T02:38:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/church-meeting-in-worker-s-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>In Labor Day, there are 2 meetings, One is Niu&rsquo;s web meeting, the othe is church&rsquo;s meeting in Xuzhou countryside.</p>

<p>I wake up at about 6:40 am and call Qing wake up.</p>

<p>And eat, and take iron plates with Qing to the school&rsquo;s door. Waited for others to go to the church meeting.</p>

<p>The place there is called 4 Pu, it means <code>Castel 4</code>, but there are not castels, lol.</p>

<p>When we get there, the others from our fellowship was still in the web meeting.</p>

<p>And I help to take the meat off from bamboo slip and string them up with iron slip.</p>

<p>It is an easy job but boring. But I am tired cause it is a good thing for others.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>Gao then tell us to go west to have a game. It is calles <em>Transfer the silent word</em></p>

<p>Then there is a family game <em>Throw and Take</em>, and we students from our school join too. And I played with a boy Su too. It is a kind of fat boy, but cute.</p>

<p>Then we get back to our camp. I still did some work to help others.</p>

<p>At noon, we ate. And the others from web meeting arrived.</p>

<p>We played other games , one is called <em>Transfer Plus Power</em>, it is a good game and a good name.</p>

<p>Zhang tell us a class about <em>Love</em> between person and person, husband and wfe, boyfriend and girl friend, and family and family. there is a book or topic called * Love&rsquo;s 5 Languages*</p>

<p>When the meeting end, we help the host to to do some farm work, just like the day&rsquo;s name, <code>Labor Day</code> It is for worker.</p>

<p>And when I went to the well, I saw a turkey, at least I think it is a turkey.</p>

<p><img src="/images/fellowship/turkey.jpg" alt="Turkey" /></p>

<p>And when I wen to the WC, I saw a <em>marsh gas pool</em>, at least I think it is too.</p>

<p><img src="/images/fellowship/gas.jpg" alt="marsh gas pool" /></p>

<p>It is my first time to see these 2 things.</p>

<p>This is a happy day. Thanks! God!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[The last day in Guangzhou -- Easter Day ]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/04_20_21-29-52.html"/>
    <updated>2014-04-20T13:29:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/21-29-52</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today is Easter Day. In the day before yesterday. When I was at Excahnge-Dream by Jiaqian in Sun Yat-sen University, I poat a post on tieba. It is about is there a fellowship in Sun Yat-sen University?</p>

<p>And I got a posiive answer. And Brother Ding tell me meet him in the Train Stop in Easter Day.</p>

<p>So today , I  have been  to Liangren Church with Brother Ding.</p>

<p>When we got there, there were just a few brothers and sisters here.And after we put bibles to the chairs. More ones came.</p>

<p>When we started, we sang a welcome song for the newers(I was new that time ).Then we sang songs to praise God. And one brother sang a song called <em>You are my favorate</em>, It is really a beautiful song (Sorry I did not remember the brother&rsquo;s name, but I record the song). And one sister who is a lead singer in the church  sang a song too, beautiful too.</p>

<p>After the Easter show, Priest Ma to teach us about <em>Jesus&rsquo;s Eternal Love</em>. It really made me moved.</p>

<p>Then our American brothers and sisters show a show about Jesus&rsquo;s Story(I recorded it too). It is a really good show.</p>

<!--more-->


<p><img src="/images/guangdong/lrchurch.jpg" alt="LiangrenChurch" /></p>

<p>In this morning. I knew two new guys, Brother Ding from Shantou and Brother Ren Xiaorong from US.</p>

<p>Xiaorong is really a open man. And he is really conscientious to learn Chinese. When we talk to Mensa and Tieba, he took seriousty to record it by phone. And he is a man who will talk to you firstly.</p>

<p>About on noon, we ate food. After that I left to train stop.</p>

<p>This is a really good and happy experience. Thanks God!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[圣诞节主题的聚会]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/12_21_sheng-dan-jie-zhu-ti-de-ju-hui.html"/>
    <updated>2013-12-21T13:20:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/sheng-dan-jie-zhu-ti-de-ju-hui</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p> 还有几天就是圣诞节，今天兄弟姐妹们提前以圣诞之名聚集在一起，感谢主。另外，Ji弟兄从澳洲回来，给大家做了一个以自己信仰和求学经历的分享。分享很不错，受益匪浅。</p>

<p> 诗歌敬拜之后，是bin哥的分享，随后就是Ji弟兄分享。最让人印象深刻的是Ji弟兄和他GF的情感历程分享，两人同在矿大团契，年级却差了三年，而两人关系确立也是在一个在澳洲、一个在国内。总之，在听两人分享时，很感动，感动两人的历程、更感动于神的大功。</p>

<p> 两人一个在赤道南、一个在赤道北，一个在太平洋南，一个在太平洋西。但这却没成为两人之间的阻隔，反而成为两人确立关系的催化剂。而在该姊妹（Sorry 还没记住名字）分享时，她做见证说（大意如下）：
  “当他发了这句<strong>耶稣爱你，我也爱你</strong>过后，我给了他发了一封邮件。当我还犹豫不决时，很多人发来的经句（没记住，但都表达出，这是神的旨意）。虽然如此，我还是决定再向神确认。我打电话给他，说这一周不要给我打电话。然后，我向神祷告，求主说，这一周谁给我第一个打电话，谁就是主您给我安排的另一半。”（可能和姊妹原话有出入，但能保证整体无误）</p>

<pre><code>结果，当晚Ji弟兄电话来了。
</code></pre>

<p> 神对这对儿弟兄姊妹的爱在这一刻就显明了。<strong>神爱世人，甚至将他的独生子赐给他们，叫一切信他的，不至灭亡，反得永生。</strong></p>

<p> <strong>主若愿意，我们就可以活着，也可以作这事，或作那事。</strong></p>

<p> <em>好久没有写golang的博文了，最近一直忙着实验报告，明天还要赶CAD作业，紧接着还有课程设计，可能Golang内容会停更一段时间，但是会保证有时间后会补回来</em></p>

<pre><code>愿主保佑这个国家！
</code></pre>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I started to read The Pilgrim’s Progress]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/12_17_i-started-to-read-the-pilgrims-progress.html"/>
    <updated>2013-12-17T12:22:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/i-started-to-read-the-pilgrims-progress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><em>The Pilgrim&rsquo;s Progress</em> was writen by John Bunyan. And it was published in Feb 1678.</p>

<p>It is a novel and it is about faith.</p>

<p>I have 2 reasons to read it.
1. Know more about faith
2. Improve my English skill</p>

<p>Moreover, there is a paper book in my school&rsquo;s library, though it is very old（about 50 years）.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[团契聚会-情欲、迷恋、真爱]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/12_07_tuan-qi-ju-hui-qing-yu-%2C-mi-lian-%2C-zhen-ai.html"/>
    <updated>2013-12-07T13:38:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/tuan-qi-ju-hui-qing-yu-,-mi-lian-,-zhen-ai</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>今天团契聚会，由于唱诗Jun有事，我替他了。分享由lin，记录由我。
lin和大家分享了-林前16:13-14</p>

<p><code>你们务要警醒，在真道上站立得稳，要作大丈夫，要刚强。凡你们所作的，都要凭爱心而作。</code>说了很多、很久。</p>

<p>Zhang姐，则继续和大家讲<strong>爱情</strong>，今天的主题是：</p>

<h3>情欲 迷恋 真爱</h3>

<!--more-->


<p>另外举了两个例子：
1. 底拿受辱     -创世纪34
2. 暗嫩和他玛  -撒母耳记下13</p>

<p>另外，我还联想到了 哥林多前书7章-<strong>婚姻的问题</strong>:</p>

<pre><code>男不近女到好。但要免淫乱的事，男子当各有自己的妻子，女子也当各有自己丈夫。

我愿众人像我一样；只是各人领受神的恩赐，一个是这样，一个是那样。
</code></pre>

<p>另外，还再次强调了<strong>婚前守贞</strong>。</p>

<p>其实Zhang姐说得对：</p>

<p>**如果两人关系已经足够亲密、足够了解，都想偷吃"禁果"，那么何不直接结婚？</p>

<p>如果还还不足够了解，又何必如此行呢？**</p>

<p><em>最近电信网络超级不稳定，文档都是写了而没有更新，见谅！</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
