<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Mensa | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/mensa/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2014-05-06T06:49:28+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Take the mensa test]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/04_21_18-00-28.html"/>
    <updated>2014-04-21T10:00:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/18-00-28</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>About 2 years ago, I wanted to join mensa. Cause in <a href="http://iqtest.dk">iqtest.dk</a>, I have gotten a 130 score.</p>

<p>But you know in 2012, the mensa.org.cn showed the number in 2012 is to achieve the max number. So I waited.</p>

<p>And the mensa.org.cn showed test will open in 2013.</p>

<p>But in 2013, the test did not open until the December in 2013.</p>

<p>And I knew there was something happen in mensa-china. But recently, the <a href="http://mensa-china.com">mensa-china.com</a> opened, although I would be in internship in April 19, I still decided to ask for leave to take the test.</p>

<p>But I found this test must be paid by paypal, and the method of paying the fee doesn&rsquo;t support alipay or unipay card.</p>

<p>So i asked Brother Jun to help me pay the fee by using his credit card(both visa and unipay). But I ignored one thing that paypal need use the credit card of the account register.</p>

<p>Then one bad thing happend. I did not pay the fee successfully, and the credit card of Brother Jun was freezed.</p>

<p>After that day, I called paypal to solve this.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>So I decide to registe a visa card, but I was just a student, so I could only a debit card, so I registed Minsheng Back Internation Debit Card(The program of regist needs 7 work days). And I asked more 2 days for leave to get the card.</p>

<p>When I came Xuzhou to get the card, I failed, cause the card did not arrive Minsheng Bank Xuzhou. I found one to transfer some dollars to my paypal account.</p>

<p>And I paid the fee.</p>

<p>In April 17, I left Pingdingshan City to Guangzhou City to take the test. In April 19, I took the test. And in the quiz after the test and a book, I got a highest score in who submit less in 25 minutes in my test batch(批次). It is really lucky, and may this little honor belong to God.</p>

<p>You know during the test, I got five or six questions too hard to solve them, just like I took the test in <a href="http://iqtest.dk">iqtest.dk</a>. But still thanks God. Because finally I paid successfully, I took the test successfully, and I arrived in Guangzhou on time and so on.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
