<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Teofl | Baham's Blog]]></title>
  <link href="http://baham.co/blog/categories/teofl/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://baham.co/"/>
  <updated>2014-11-27T10:54:42+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://baham.co/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Baham]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Toefl Test I Took.]]></title>
    <link href="http://baham.co/07_10_toefl-test-i-took.html"/>
    <updated>2014-07-10T08:02:00+00:00</updated>
    <id>http://baham.co/toefl-test-i-took</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>This is my first time to take Toefl Test. After I graduated and left the camp. I prepared for the toefl test. But I didn&rsquo;t prepared it well. I even not finished the one whole office guide test. It is really a pity. Wahtever, the porpose I take it is just verified my English skill, although the scores did not public, but the I achive the porpose, my English-skill is bad.</p>

<p>What I need do is learning and practicing.</p>

<p>The 4 parts in toefl, I nearlly did not finished one of them well.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>In Reading Section, After I finished the first one, I found I did not have enought time . And I feel nervous, and you know, many answers are guessed by me.</p>

<p>And the listening section, what I pay the muchest time to practice, but what I can understand is just a little. And I was too tired to concentrate on the convesations or lecture. This is a lesson, when you take the test, you must sleep well and enough.</p>

<p>Then it is speaking, I found I can not read the paragraphes on time. As for the questions about speaking by oneself, I could not prepare them well in 15 seconds. I need to practice thinking in the heart with English.</p>

<p>What is the last is Writing Section. Maybe it will gave me the best score in 4 parts. But you know, they are still not good articles, it&rsquo;s just like an articles that writen by a pupil. not like an article by a high school graduation.</p>

<p>What I need to practice and learn is very much.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
